本字幕由 YYeTs人人影視 翻譯創作
歡迎愛好者加入我們  www.YYeTs.net
■
翻譯：lncpeter   望月者   不可云   Garfield2974   哈米波青   noanothertony 校對：海因里希
后期：☆☆
■
墨西哥某地
只有無比頑固的美國佬才會來這鳥不拉屎的地方
Only a hardheaded gringo... Would come down here...
執行什么援救計劃  而且居然是單槍匹馬
On a rescue mission... ALL ALONE
這美國佬不肯開口說話
This gringo is not going to talk.
那就殺了他
Then kill him.
速度點  將軍在等著我們呢
C'mon, the General's expecting us.
你不能用自己的槍
You can't use your gun...
用他自己的槍射殺他
...Shoot him with his.
這槍用不了
It's not working.
這兔崽子的槍連撞針都沒有
This asshole's gun has no firing pin.
別管他了
Leave him.
狗狗們好久沒試過自己殺死獵物了
The dogs haven't had to kill for their food in a while.
朋友  下次
Next time, amigo,
先計劃好再來
plan ahead.
我真是個偽天主教徒
Oh, I'm such a bad Catholic.
才不  你就是腦子有病罷了
No, you're just sick in the head.
別忘了要拿給將軍的錢
Don't forget the General's money.
那美國佬賄賂錯警察了
That gringo bribed the wrong cop...
還帶了一把沒撞針的槍
...and brought a gun with no firing pin.
撞針在這里
"戰神"  史密斯上校
追蹤中
聯邦警察
墨西哥另外某地
"怪頭"  博斯克·拜庫斯
傻蛋  我心肝寶貝呢
Where's my girl, fool?
她很好  就在那里面  她好得不得了
She cool, man. She in there. She's still fine as hell.
就這樣嗎  你在巴達被轟出局了嗎
So that's it? Bada-bing, you out of the game?
生意都吹了嗎
Done with the whole trade?
-對  -問題就在這  博斯克
- Yeah.  - Well, that's the problem, Bosco.
要么繼續  要么就在墨西哥
You either keep doing that,
監獄好好呆上十五年
or you do a 15- year bid in a Mexican prison
和齊拓表兄一起
with Cheeto's cousin in there.
還是老一套  你自己收拾爛攤子吧  哥們
Same old shit. You choose how to flush the toilet, brother.
好了  吃軟的還是吃硬的
That's right. Easy way or the hard way.
可憐蟲
來呀
Come on!
裝毛的街頭霸王  靠
Okay, street soldier. Shit.
注意點  怪頭  你連我這老朋友都要失去了
But watch yourself, B.A., now, you gonna lose your oldest friend here.
傻瓜
還好嗎  心肝  想我嗎
What's up, girl? You miss me?
我可想死你了  真的  我們分離太久了  寶貝
Because l missed you. Yes, l did. It's been too long, baby.
太久太久了
Way too long.
鬼地方
Heck of a place.
這鬼地方還真漂亮
Just a heck of a beautiful place.
這是分時使用的嗎  我也想享用
ls this a time- share? l'd love to get in on this.
我很喜歡你這的圣非氣氛  圖克
l like this whole Santa Fe motif you got going here, Tuco.
圣非  美國新墨西哥州首府
很有亞利桑那的味道  也很有美國墨西哥人的風范  真好
It's very Arizona, very Tex-Mex. It's good. It's good.
不如我們把我六點鐘方向的那人叫來
Maybe we can get the guy at my six
做一些墨西哥荷葉餅怎么樣
to whip up a couple of quesadiches, you know?
"小白臉"  派克中尉
我要火星人都看得到這燃燒的火焰
l want the flames to be seen by the Martians.
美國佬
Americano, gringo.
-軍隊情報人員  -你在說誰
- Army lntelligence.  - Who's that?
-你啊  老兄  -不是吧
- You, man.  - No.
看來也不怎么聰明  都困在輪胎里面了
You're not so intelligent because you're stuck in some tires.
我很開心  真開心
I'm happy. I'm happy.
這再好不過了吧
Doesn't get any better than this, right?
-我定是在夢里  -是呀
- I'm living the dream.  - You are!
你不是來這里
You're gonna come here...
把我裝進袋子丟出邊界的嗎
...to throw me in a bag across the border...
但你卻在那和我妻子盡情云雨
...but instead you have sex with my wife.
首先她實在太性感了
Well, first of all, she's so hot,
而且我們兩個都恨你  所以就
and we both hate you. So that's just sort of how it...
-早上好  -早上好  伙計
- Good morning!  - Good morning, man!
這才是真正的派對
Now it's a party!
-你就這點能耐嗎  -這才是真正的派對  伙計
- ls that your best shot?  - Now it's a party, man!
見鬼了
Oh, hell, no.
慢慢移過去
Slide over slowly.
你是在攔路搶劫嗎
You jacking me?
這算什么  太陽從西邊出來了嗎
What is this, opposite day?
我不是搶劫犯  但如果我不及時趕到  我朋友就會死
I'm not a thief. But if l don't reach my friend in time, then he dies.
如果你不是搶劫犯  我敢保證你也不是一個殺手
lf you ain't a thief, l guarantee you ain't a killer.
左手放開方向盤  右手松開離合器  快
Take your left hand off the wheel and your right hand off the shifter now.
你不會朝我頭開槍的  大叔
You ain't gonna shoot me in the head, pops.
你自己心里清楚
You know that ain't happening.
你他媽的有病嗎
What the hell's wrong with you, man?
隨隨便便就開槍打陌生人
You shoot a total stranger?
我都不認識你  操
l don't even know you, fool. Damn.
這點傷死不了
It'll heal, l promise.
-用這個包起來  -我知道怎么做止血帶  笨蛋
- Here, wrap it in this.  - l know how to make a tourniquet, fool.
我知道那很痛  但我必須讓你明白
l know it hurts, but l had to make a point with you.
你以為是這把我惹毛了嗎  才不是
That ain't what's pissing me off.
是你射到我的寶貝車  這惹毛了老子
You shooting my van is what's pissing me off, man.
你腦子有病嗎
What's wrong with you?
你是陸軍游騎兵嗎  小子
You Army Ranger, son?
大叔  小心斟酌你要說的下一句話
Be real careful of what you say next, pops.
要是敢污蔑我的隊伍  就準備好被我塞進引擎箱吧
And be ready to empty that burner if you start shit-talking my battalion.
從不讓我的戰友失望
Never shall I fail my comrades.
英勇的向全世界宣告我就是救世主
Gallantly will I show the world that I am a specially selected soldier.
若遇到敵人  我會充滿干勁
Energetically will l meet the enemies of my country.
我將在戰場上把他們擊敗
I shall defeat them on the field of battle
因為我比他們更強
for l am better trained.
我會竭盡全力去拼
And I will fight with all my might.
漢尼拔·史密斯上校  第75游騎兵團
Colonel Hannibal Smith. 75th Ranger Regiment.
我是4營的  在佐治亞州本寧堡駐防
4th Battalion. Fort Benning, Georgia.
游騎兵總部
你是大名鼎鼎的人物  我是怪頭拜庫斯下士
l know who you are, sir. Corporal B.A. Baracus.
我聽說是因為莫須有的罪名而被開除軍籍和解除武裝
l mean, it was till l was dishonorably discharged for some bullshit.
下士  我不相信巧合
l don't subscribe to coincidence, Corporal.
我相信無論表面上看起來顯得多么混亂
l believe that, no matter how random things might appear,
本質上總是有計劃存在
there's still a plan.
我們把他喂狗了
We fed him to the dogs.
墨西哥荒漠中
That here in the middle of the Mexican desert,
在我最需要幫助的時候
when l needed him most,
我找到了一個游騎兵伙伴
l'd find a fellow Ranger.
伙計
Boy.
現在我需要你幫我去救另一個同伴
Now, l need your help to save another.
壞消息
Bad news for you today!
你等的那個救援人員  我們都把他喂給羅威納犬咯
This rescue that's coming, we fed him to the Rottweilers
-早在一個小時之前  -好笑的是
- about an hour ago.  - You know what's funny?
你以為你抓住我了嗎
ls that you actually believe that you got me.
你真以為你殺得了我嗎
You actually think you're gonna kill me.
你還能開車嗎
Can you drive?
保證讓你大吃一驚  長官
Better than anybody you've ever seen, sir.
以前沒人知道你藏在哪里
Nobody knew where you were hiding...
以前沒有情報  不過到此為止了  蠢貨
There was no intel...until now, asshole.
兩分鐘之內  我就會去享受冰鎮啤酒
In a few minutes I'm gonna be having a cold beer,
而你則烈火燒身  保重了  我的朋友
and you are gonna be on fire. Take care, my friend.
-草  泥    -不
- Alpha, Mike...  - No!
馬
...Foxtrot.
好好想想吧
Think about it.
操你媽的  永別了
Adios! Mother Fu...
漢尼拔
Hannibal!
你搞什么
What are you doing?
進去
Get in!
怪頭  快走
B.A., move.
真他媽的
This is bullshit!
又跑了一個
Ahora, muerto!
停下來  拜托
Stop it! Please stop!
停下來  停下來  拜托  停下來吧
Please stop! Stop it! Stop! Please stop!
你這一天過得如何
How's your day going?
這滋味肯定不好受
This is not going to taste good.
寶貝  我剛吐完
Baby, l just threw up.
你等我嚼點口香糖先
Let me get some gum. Let me just get some gum.
你看到了嗎  你看到圖克的臉色了嗎
Did you see that? Did you see Tuco's face?
你過來的時候簡直叫人難以相信
When you came over, that was unbelievable!
-你要我說多少遍  -我說你真會算時間呀
- How many times did l say it?  - The timing was perfect.
-小白  你到底要我說多少次  -那太漂亮了
- How many times did I say it, Face?  - It was so beautiful.
-我叫你干掉圖克一個人就好  -啥
- I told you not to take down Tuco alone.  - What?
那啥  你
Well, you...
好吧  我很抱歉
You know what? I'm sorry.
我很抱歉  沒按戰神大人的意思去做
I'm sorry l didn't have the Hannibal Smith How-to Manual.
-但是我必須得行動  -你的行動闖了大禍  小白
- Okay? l had to move.  - And that move snowballs, Face.
你差點害死你自己
You almost got yourself killed.
你還差點害死我  還差點害死他
Which almost got me killed and almost got him killed.
幼稚
Five-year-old.
你看起來好屌的樣子
You look like you got a real bad attitude.
啥
What?
我有開槍打壞你的車嗎
Did I shoot up your van?
我穿走了你最中意的襯衣嗎
Am I wearing your favorite shirt?
這是你最中意的襯衣嗎
This is your favorite shirt?
是的  靚仔  這件就是
Yeah, pretty boy, that's my favorite shirt.
你還為我挨槍子了嗎
Did you get shot for me, too?
-車還被搶了  -我搶的
- And carjacked.  - By me.
等下  他搶了你車還讓你充當司機
Wait, and he still got you to drive?
多謝了  我是派克
Thank you. Peck.
我是拜庫斯  沒什么
Baracus. It's all good.
看到了吧  小白  這就是沒有按計劃來的下場
See, Face, this is what happens when we forget about plans
盲目開火
and just fire blind.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我又不是圣賢  咋能不犯錯
I'm so sorry that l have feelings for a human being,
-我愛上一妞  -愛
- that l fell in love.  - Love?
等等  那三周前那個克羅地亞妞呢
Wait a minute. What about Miss Croatia three weeks ago?
滿足生理需要而已
Rescue sex.
我只是想救她
l was just trying to save her.
-救她  -嗯哼
- Save her?  - Yeah.
救她嗎  怎么救
Save her? How?
得了  你有什么計劃  說來聽聽  小白
Please, do share with us your plan, Face.
好吧  我還沒想過什么計劃
Okay, I hadn't thought about that yet.
我就說吧  最后還得我來
Exactly. I had to.
她的飛機票
Her plane ticket.
工作簽證和新的護照
Her work visa and her new passport.
別跟我說些為了救她之類的蠢話  小白
And don't bullshit me that this was about her, Face.
這只是為了干掉圖克
This was all about Tuco.
還有彈夾嗎
Do you have a mag?
墨西哥
美國陸軍醫院
索諾拉
保羅圣維森特醫院
-麥克  -頭兒  你怎么了
- Mike.  - Boss man. How the hell are you?
-還在這滿天塵土中活著呀  -很不走運吧
- Still chewing the same dirt?  - I am, unfortunately.
-大老遠的來到美麗的墨西哥  -不錯
- And out here in lovely Mexico.  - Good.
-你有什么給我  -我安排了精干人員在附近盯著
- So what have you got for me?  - I got a fast bird doing pizza runs.
-行動代號是賽蒂斯之斧  -斧頭嗎  好
- The call sign is "Hatchet."  - Hatchet. Okay.
就是個名字而已
And that is whatever you want it to be.
這是給你的
This is yours.
不需我提醒你  他們不能到了美國佬手中
General, may I remind you, they don't take to the gringos.
我欠你個人情
I owe you one, okay?
-快快上路吧  -三年都等了
- Let's not wait till Bragg again, huh?  - Three years.
-還有孩子  想你哦  -怪頭  -怎么了
- And the kid. Still you and the chicks.  - B.A.  - What?
我怎么能就這樣丟下我的心肝寶貝
How am l gonna just leave my girl like this, after all that?
我可是大打出手才把她搶回來
l had to fight to get her back.
取下車鑰匙  到時再回來取她
Leave the keys and we'll come back for her. Come on.
看著好破爛呀
Looking shabby.
-怎么打  伙計  -遇佛殺佛
- What is the deal, brother?  - Shoot anything that moves, okay?
-這比在哥倫比亞還糟  -我了解圖克  伙計
- This is worse than Colombia.  - I know Tuco, man.
別擔心  我會帶她到圣特魯佩斯的軍事學院
Don't worry about it. I'll take her to war college in Saint Tropez.
我會把他們所有人全引來  別有后顧之憂
I'll get you all their numbers, so don't worry about it.
-小白  照顧下怪頭  -好
- Face, look after the Corporal.  - Yeah. Okay.
有意思的是  你全身上下都是汽油味
And you're covered in gas, which I think is interesting.
去找大夫看看你的傷  下士
Find a treatment room, Corporal.
趕緊的  我去找我們的飛行員
Make it quick. I'm gonna find our pilot.
大夫  你有空來看看這個傷者嗎
Hey, Doc, you got a second for a wounded vet?
小瘋魔  默多克上尉
花瓶戰斗機飛行員
Highly decorated combat pilot.
但你問他  他絕對會說自己最出色
You ask him, he thinks he's the best in the world.
但他是個還有點用的瘋子
But he's a functioning lunatic.
上周他想修好一輛救護車用來逃跑
Last week he tried to escape by jump-starting an ambulance.
完畢
Clear.
見鬼
Damn it!
我就喜歡這種人
My kind of guy.
差點就刺到你的紋身了
lt almost hit your tattoo there.
有人見到默多克先生嗎
Has anyone seen Mr. Murdock?
-舊式游騎兵紋身  -默多克先生
- The old Ranger tat.  - Mr. Murdock?
要是我說我也有  你會覺得我瘋了嗎
Would you think l was crazy if l told you l had one of these?
你看錯了
Something wrong with your eyes, man.
-默多克先生  -我在給病人縫合傷口呢  護士
- Mr. Murdock?  - Not while I'm operating, nurse.
-別吵我  -你怎么從病房里跑出來了
- Not now.  - Why are you off the ward?
有人放屁了嗎  是你嗎
ls that gas? ls that you?
-我聞到了  -病房是什么意思
- l smell gas.  - What do you mean, "ward"?
-什么病房  -他是這里的病人
- What ward?  - This man is a patient here.
是你嗎  別聽她的  她瘋了
ls this you? Don't listen to her, she's crazy.
老實說  我還是霍普金斯大學的實習醫生呢
Honestly, I'm a practicing doctor at Johns Hopkins University.
你叫他給你縫成閃電狀的嗎  -根本沒呀
- Did you ask him to do a lightning bolt?  - I asked for no lightning bolt.
-我要叫保安  -這個瘋子
- I'm calling security.  - What's wrong with this fool?
-他瘋了吧  -你才瘋了
- Is he crazy?  - It is you.
-你著火了  兄弟  -啥  搞什么
- You on fire, man.  - What? What's that?
-搞毛  -天呀
- What the...  - Oh, Jesus!
-我太喜歡你們游騎兵了   -你腦子注水了嗎
- You Rangers. I like you!  - Are you crazy?
喂  住手
Hey! Hey, come on!
下士  退后
Corporal, off. Back off!
這里可是醫院
This is a hospital.
-大家都見過默多克先生咯  -何止見過
- Everybody's met Mr. Murdock.  - Met him?
他還在我手臂上縱火
He lit my arm on fire.
他還把我的傷口縫成閃電狀
He stitched a lightning bolt in mine, man.
看著我  小子
Look at me, son.
據說你是個超棒的直升機飛行員
I'm told you're a hell of a chopper pilot.
是最好的  長官
The best, sir.
我才不坐這瘋子開的直升飛機
I'm not getting on a chopper with this nut job.
好極了  他也是你計劃的一部分嗎
Yeah, that's a good... ls he another one of your projects?
我是貨真價實的戰士  我是個游騎兵
I'm a real soldier. I'm a Ranger, baby.
壓力真大
I'm worried!
我真是個游騎兵  長官
I'm a Ranger, sir.
這對我來說就足夠了
That's good enough for me.
你被我們接管
You have been released into our care
-并恢復上尉軍銜  -這對我來說太不爽了
- and reinstated, Captain.  - I'm not even close to good with that.
謝謝你  長官
Thank you, sir.
我們離開這鬼地方吧
Let's get the hell out of here.
你這魅力無窮的破爛呀
You gorgeous old rust bucket, you.
想我沒有
Did you miss your daddy?
小白  知道計劃萬無一失  最重要的是什么嗎
Face, what's the most important part of a well-oiled plan?
要占據先機
To be one step ahead of the enemy,
-而不是落荒而逃  -誰說我們要逃跑了
- not to be running away from him.  - Who says we're running?
什么  我們要和那瘋子
What, we're going to go in this dinosaur
-一起鉆進這骨灰級灰機里嗎  -嗯哼
- with this freak show?  - Yep.
你把我迷得團團轉  團團轉
You spin me right round, baby Right round
-螺旋翼沒問題  長官  -這家伙到底是誰
- Rotors are good, sir.  - Who is this guy?
快點  我們走
Come on! Let's go!
干掉美國佬
We've got gringos to kill!
默多克  把這玩意弄上天去
Murdock, get this thing in the air.
抓緊咯
Hold on, boys!
我要試試在卡通里看到的把戲
I'm gonna try something l saw in a cartoon once.
你說卡通是毛意思  快把我們弄走
What you talking about cartoons for? Get us the hell out of here!
六點鐘方向有敵方直升機
We got a hot chopper to your six.
金剛罩  你們打不到我  打不到我
I'm blocking bullets. We're bulletproof.
金剛罩  打不到我
We're bulletproof, boys!
小心
Oh, heads up.
我看見你了  美國佬
I see you, gringo!
你把我的心肝寶貝壓成了薄餅  我要殺了你這混蛋
You pancaked my van! I'm gonna kill you, fool!
你不能停在那里  那是殘疾人專用的
You can't park there. That's a handicap zone.
-我就知道你是個瘋子  神經病  -我已經后悔了
- l knew you was crazy! l knew...  - This is a mistake.
開火
Fire! Fire! Fire!
把他們打下來
Blow them out of the sky.
我從來沒有這樣試過
I've never tried this before!
你看到了嗎
Did you see that?
你看到他讓直升飛機做空翻了嗎
Did you see how he turned the helicopter?
這空對空作戰真刺激  是不  老兄
Whoa! There's nothing like some good air-to-air combat, eh, boys?
別看我  看前面
Don't look at me! Look there!
他只剩熱感導彈了
He's only got heat seekers left.
上尉  把我們弄走
Captain, get us out of here.
抓緊了  這可不好受
Hold on, this could get ugly!
準備好  加油啊  寶貝  繼續爬升
Here we go! Come on, baby, climb!
發射導彈
Fire the missiles.
哇哇  導彈  來吧
Whoa! Missiles! Come on, come on.
這就是對付熱感導彈的方法
That's how we deal with heat seekers, chaps.
我們熄火
We go cold.
搞毛
What the hell?
小白  快把他弄進來
Face, get him in here!
媽了個逼的
Holy, shit! Oh, shit!
抓住他了
Got him!
重啟
Restart. Restart.
關好門
Close the door!
我知道你是空降兵  但那也太夸張了吧
l know you're Airborne Rangers, but that was ridiculous!
你會沒事的
You're gonna be okay.
頭兒  我們是要殺了圖克  不是被殺
Boss, the idea is to kill Tuco, not the other way around!
搶先一步并不是計劃  小子
One step ahead of the game isn't a plan, kid.
而是要搶先兩三步
Two to three steps ahead.
搶在敵人出招前就將其拿下
Beating an enemy's move before it's even made.
這才是計劃
That's a plan.
斧頭  斧頭  瞄準尾隨我的目標
Hatchet, Hatchet, lock on my LC.
圖克將軍  你現在正未經許可
General Tuco, you are currently engaged
對美國軍事人員發動攻擊
in unauthorized warfare on United States military personnel.
滾你媽的  是你先挑起來的
No, no, no, no, no, no, no! You engaged me.
重復一遍
Repeat.
你現在正未經許可對美國軍事人員發動攻擊
You are engaged in unauthorized warfare on United States military personnel.
而且還在美國領空
Over United States air space.
-什么 - 草  泥
- What?  - Alpha, Mike...
馬
Foxtrot!
-換句話說  操  你  媽  -不
- ln other words, Adios! Mother- fu...!!  - Oh, no.
干得漂亮  上尉
Well done, Captain.
-酷斃了  -酷個屁
- That was awesome.  - That wasn't awesome.
-你真是個天才  -老子死也不坐飛機了
- You are a genius!  - I'm never flying again in this thing!
相信你果然沒錯  頭兒
l never should have doubted you, boss!
凡事都在計劃之中  小子
There's a plan in everything, kid.
我就愛計劃圓滿的那一刻
And I love it when a plan comes together.
天龍特攻隊
八年
八十次成功任務之后
前線作戰基地  獵頭
美軍撤離伊拉克前最后的日子
沒有比這更好的烹飪了
Gunpowder cooking. Nothing like it.
小白  你想要用凝固汽油紅燒還是用原子彈油炸
Face, you want it napalmed or nuked?
原子彈油炸
Nuke it.
油炸
Nuke it!
默多克  他媽的給我煮熟一點
Murdock, burn the hell out of it,
給我狠狠地燒
like it was damned.
把整個地方都燒了算了  兄弟
Burn the whole place down, buddy.
阿帕奇   武裝偵察直升機
-你要私家秘調醬汁嗎  -不不不  不要防凍劑那玩意
- You want secret sauce?  - No, no, no. None of that anti-freeze.
秘密就是  你有病  地球人都知道
The secret's out. You crazy. Everybody knows.
沒人能學會你的防凍腌泡汁  默多克
No one can do an anti- freeze marinade like you can, Murdock.
但我上次吃了以后就面癱了
But l got a little Bell's palsy last time l ate that.
只是局部面癱而已  來吧  有點男人樣
It's only partial paralysis. Come on, take it like a man.
是的  長官  正要準備和他們對話
Yes, sir. I'm having that conversation right now.
一定會讓他們明白的  一切都在我掌控  長官
We will enforce that. I've got it well in hand, sir.
我想你也不希望我局部面癱地上戰場吧
I don't think you want me to be in the field partially paralyzed, bud.
有客人喲
Visitors.
說真的  我還真吃了一驚
Wow, I'm a little taken aback. I'm not gonna lie.
中尉
Lieutenant.
很抱歉  我是不是也要叫你中尉
Oh, I'm sorry, am l supposed to call you Lieutenant back?
不  你得叫我上尉
No, you're supposed to call me Captain.
上尉
Captain. Captain?
沒錯
That's right.
讓我想起吃的了  瞧瞧你
Captain Crunch. Look at you. Wow.
餐廳名
怪不得你不要孩子  也不要家庭
So, l guess you said no to the kids, no to the family.
就是要平步青云啊
Just no ladder you can't climb, huh?
不  親愛的  我只是不要你而已
No, no, honey, l just said no to you.
你好呀  我叫珀西
Hello. My name's Percy.
要吃豬肉嗎
Would you like some pork?
我要是把你丫手打折了  你還能再傻逼一點么
lf I broke every bone in your hand, could you still do that?
太不可思議了  三年了
This is crazy. Three years?
我們三年沒見面了
We haven't seen each other for three years,
你就是來談這個的嗎
this is what we're gonna talk about?
那你想談什么
What would you like to discuss?
鄉村音樂泰斗
我那張斯蒂利·丹的CD帶來了么
Did you take my Steely Dan CD?
我都懶的搭理你
I'm not even going to respond to that.
我們一口氣聽了九遍
We listened to it, like, nine times in a row.
品著那難喝的解百衲葡萄酒  記得嗎
We were drinking that crappy cabernet. You remember that?
我們還干了點兒別的  咱干什么了
We were doing something else. What were we doing?
你還記得嗎  干什么了  在臥室里
Do you remember what it was we were doing? It was in a bedroom.
你都忘了嗎
You don't remember?
我只記得我離開了你
The only thing I remember is leaving.
這是我對你最美好的回憶
Which is my fondest memory of you.
你們是最棒的  可別給我惹事
You guys are the best. Stay out of trouble, you hear me?
保重  謝謝
Take care. Yes. Thank you.
頭盔戴牢了
Keep that on.
上校  我叫林奇  中央情報局的
Colonel, my name is Lynch, I'm with Central lntelligence.
在之前第一次"沙漠風暴"行動時遇見一個中情局的人也叫林奇
l knew a company man named Lynch back in the first Desert Storm.
對  我們那有一堆人叫都叫這名兒
Yeah, l come from a long line of Lynches.
有想過人們為何不信任中情局嗎
You ever stop to consider that maybe the reason nobody trusts the CIA
因為沒人知道你們的真名
is because nobody knows your real names?
有什么可效勞的嗎  林奇先生
What can l do for you, Mr. Lynch?
我要你幫我阻止薩達姆的前任手下
I need you to help me to stop Saddam's former flunkies
在未來的30小時內竊取數十億美元
from stealing over a billion dollars in the next 30 hours.
現今我國境外唯一一個印制美元的鑄幣廠
Now, the only mint outside of the U.S. capable of printing our money
在伊朗境內
belonged to the Shah of lran.
曾在兩伊戰爭期間失蹤
During the lran- lraq War, it went missing.
流言盛傳是薩達姆偷去了
Rumor was, Saddam had stolen it.
"沙漠風暴"時我們已經偷了回來
And we stole it back during Desert Storm.
但是沒拿回模板
Well, you didn't get the engraving plates.
那不要緊
It didn't matter.
他們要想印鈔票就得重建鑄幣廠
They would have had to rebuild a mint just to print those bills.
沒錯  長官
Well, sir,
他們正在這么干
it's happening as we speak.
這群阿拉伯來的暴徒占用了廢棄的伊拉克國家鑄幣廠
Fedayeen thugs have seized what's left of the lraqi National Mint
印制了幾十億非法美國貨幣
to run off billions of dollars in unbacked American currency.
他們要如何把模板和十億美鈔
How are they planning on moving the plates and a billion dollars
-運出巴格達  -裝甲車
- out of Baghdad?  - Armored convoy,
由退伍的伊拉克特種兵駕駛
manned with former lraqi spec ops.
速度奇快  遇佛殺佛
You know, high speed, shoot-to-kill types.
你打算怎樣阻止他們
So how do you plan on stopping them?
聽著  最近有流言說薩達姆的黨羽
Listen, there's some rumors about some top-secret plates
要把一些高度機密的模板偷運出城
being smuggled out of the city by Saddam loyalists.
你聽說了嗎
Do you know anything about this?
你聽好了  要是你想借此事大顯身手
Seriously, if you're going to make a play for these plates,
我可得請你滾蛋了
I'm waving you off right now.
因為那是我的職責  我能搞定
'Cause it's my responsibility and it's my ass.
我是認真的
I'm serious.
小白
Face?
不然我把你告上軍事法庭
l will court-martial you.
-好吧  -嘿
- Whoo! Okay.  - Hey.
別拿我的話當耳邊風
Get the memo.
記得告訴你家親愛的史密斯上校他媽的給我離巴格達越遠越好
Tell your beloved Colonel Smith and stay the hell out of Baghdad.
你
You know,
你再也沒回來  我以為你會回來
you never came back. l thought you were gonna come back.
我現在不是回來了么
Well, this is me, coming back.
你覺得那幾個小丑真敢插手
You think those clowns can really pull this off?
聽著  這話我從來說不出口
Listen, listen, l would never tell him this,
但他們確實是四個分隊里最牛逼的小組
but they are the best CIAndestine unit in the four branches,
而且最擅長那些不可思議的任務
and they specialize in the ridiculous...
我去找其他人
...shadow peck and the rest of them.
-給我盯緊了他們  -遵命  長官
- Do not let them out of your sight.  - Yes, ma'am.
"暗黑破壞神"是惡魔的意思嗎  -當然啦
- Doesn't diablo mean "devil"?  - Yeah, man.
去你娘的  漢尼拔  你想要我怎么樣
God damn it, Hannibal, what do you want me to do?
羅素·莫里森將軍
基地指揮官
如果這是我的行動
If this were my operation and you wanted it,
-那你隨便插手  可這不是  -你竟讓"黑森林"執行這任務
- you would have the mission.  - You let Black Forest deploy on this,
這是國際性事件  我向你保證
and it's an international incident, l promise you.
他們根本不算是士兵
They're not soldiers.
就是群混在軍隊里的紈?子弟
They're frat boys with trigger fingers.
-誰指揮地面部隊  -布拉德·帕克
- Who's running the ground team?  - Brock Pike.
帕克
Pike.
他就是個搞笑的暴徒  得了吧
He's a thug. He's a cartoon character. Come on.
漢尼拔  我們有命令在身
Hannibal, we have been ordered, ordered, mind you,
明確要你別靠近巴格達
to stay out of Baghdad.
-就這么定了  不得違抗  -將軍
- Cut, dried, the end.  - General,
我們得給他點回旋余地  您覺得呢
we should find him a little wiggle room, don't you think?
我還認識一個叫林奇的中情局走狗
You know, l knew another Lynch, a CIA stooge.
68年時駐扎在老撾
Stationed in Laos, '68.
-和我沒關系  -真的嗎
- No relation.  - Are you sure?
我一看你就想起他
'Cause you remind me of him.
我幾小時后得趕到喀布爾
I'm due in Kabul in a few hours.
希望我48小時后回來時已經萬事大吉
I'll be back here in 48. I'm assuming we're green and go.
要是干砸了別忘通知我
Notify me otherwise.
他在總部還穿著防彈衣
He's wearing body armor in the HQ.
能看出中情局的都什么貨色了吧
And that should tell you everything you need to know about the CIA.
老羅   現在沒其他人了  咱們談談
Russ, let's do some good on the way out the door here.
那些模板的危害性太大
Those plates are gonna do all kinds of damage.
讓我去搞定
Let me go get them.
算了吧  漢尼拔  這次你要置身事外
Forget about it, Hannibal. Steer clear of this one.
不要插手
Well clear of it.
這次行動是直刺薩德爾城的心臟
This is a gauntlet run right through the heart of Sadr City.
薩達姆·侯賽因是個公認的瘋子
Saddam Hussein was a certifiable madman,
但還沒瘋狂到
but even he wasn't crazy enough
三十年后再去那地方
to go into that place more than once in 30 years.
我們一周前撤離   那里已經無法無天了
We pulled out of there a week ago and already it's the Wild West.
你聽上去還是很擔心的
You actually sound worried.
你還是生氣了
And you actually seem offended.
不是說你不如當年了
Well, this isn't about you losing a step now.
我想你要明白這一點
l want you to know that.
我可比當年強大得多
I'm 10 times the man l was when you met me.
也迅捷得多
And twice as fast.
老羅
Russ,
我和弟兄們保證能全身而退
the boys and l can get this done, minus the bloodshed.
那些模板的危害性太大
Those plates can do all kinds of damage.
別逼我求你
Don't make me beg.
我不想看到你求人
I'd hate to see you beg, Hannibal.
你和我是這么多年的老朋友
You've been my friend for a long time.
更重要的是
More importantly,
你和那些小伙子們可能是
you and those boys have possibly been
我調遣過的最有價值的戰斗力
the most valuable military asset l have ever had at my disposal.
你請求我別逼你求我
Now, you asked me not to make you beg.
但其實是我得求你
Right now, I'm begging you.
漢尼拔  求你了  這次你就放手吧
Hannibal, please, let this one go.
老羅   事關重大  不能讓那幫笨蛋上呀
Russ, this is too big an enterprise. We can't let these bozos do this.
事關重大呀
It's way too big.
你是否愿意帶著我的祝福出戰
And you'd do it with or without my blessing?
我不會不帶的
No, that I wouldn't.
我需要你的祝福
l need your blessing.
我不敢肯定這算不算是種祝福
I'm not so sure that it is a blessing.
祝你馬到功成  伙計
Good hunting, my friend.
謝謝
Thank you.
和老家伙談的如何
How'd it go with the old man?
都是些陳詞濫調   你手上是什么
Same old, same old. What you got there?
我的新歡
Pictures of my new baby.
不錯呀  眼光不賴
Oh, look at her. Who's a proud papa?
這些是默多克近距離拍下的
These pictures are the closest Murdock gets to that van.
等我回到洛杉磯  它就會在那兒等我了
It's ready for me when I go back to LA.
聽著  怪頭  我們得多待一陣子了
Listen, B.A., we're extending our stay a little bit.
得回巴格達去
We're going back into Baghdad.
上頭不是命令咱別去巴格達嗎
l thought we was ordered to stay out of Baghdad.
-沒錯  可我   -史密斯
- That's true, but I'm...  - Smith.
-帕克  -我聽說你和你手下
- Pike.  - l understand you and your grunts
要搶我飯碗  我可不太高興
are now stealing my gigs. l don't like that.
我以為你們"黑森林"大軍忙著
I figured you Black Forest guys would be busy
在哪搞獨裁或推翻民主呢
installing a dictatorship or overthrowing a democracy somewhere.
現在是周末  那些事得上班時間處理  大叔
It's still the weekend, yet. That's nine-to-five stuff, pops.
看看你們這群小丑
Look at you clowns.
你們算哪門子士兵
You're not soldiers.
簡直就是穿著馬球衫的刺客
You're assassins in polo shirts.
你們折騰一年的活兒  我們一周就能拿下
We'll make in a week what you guys make in a year.
鈔票買不來勇氣  小子
Cash don't buy guts, kid,
也買不來智慧
or brains.
可惜你兩樣都缺
And you're short on both.
這是莫里森的基地  趕緊滾出我的地盤
This is Morrison's base. Bug out of my op.
怪頭  你都穿上黃色領騎衫了呀
They make you wear the yellow shirt there, B.A.?
你名字是啥意思   廢物的意思嗎
What's that stand for, "Barely Able"?
讓開  廢物
Get out of my way, punk.
別怕他們
Hey, don't sweat them.
他們可幫我們大忙了
They might have just done us a favor. A big one.
看   只剩一輛中型坦克了
Let me see, we got one medium tank left.
我跟你說  她不會平白無故地回來
I'm telling you, there's a reason she came back.
小白  我都說了  忘了她
Face, l told you, forget about her.
這女人的野心簡直
The levels of ambition on this woman...
打死我也不坐飛機了  漢尼拔
I ain't stepping foot in any type of aircraft, Hannibal.
不論是滑翔機  紙飛機  還是輕型機
No gliders, paper planes, ultra-lights.
-你就是揪著這事兒不放吧  -沒錯
- You ever gonna let me live that down?  - No.
墨西哥那都多久前的事了  我還救了你的命
Mexico was a long time ago, and l saved your life.
那你怎么不謝我在醫院里沒揍爛你菊花
How about thanking me for not whooping your ass at the hospital?
沒遇見你之前我是空降兵
l was an Airborne Ranger until l met you.
可你嚇得跟什么似的
And you chickened out just like...
-263次跳傘  -你就不能謝謝我嗎
- 263 jumps.  - Just a thank-you would have been nice.
可坐過一次你開的直升機后全毀了
And one helicopter ride with you screws it up.
空降兵卻恐飛  就是個棒槌
Airborne Ranger with a fear of flying. Like a punk!
怪頭  我保證  咱搶過卡車
B.A., for the last time, nobody leaves the truck
后就都在里面呆著  好吧
once we take it over. Okay?
我老表帶我來到這個派對  在那里有個超棒的伴奏樂隊
My cousin takes me to this party where this amazing cover band
演奏了鞭撻金屬版的萊昂納爾·里奇的懷舊金曲
does this trash metal version of Hello by Lionel Richie.
-哦  -唱起來就像這樣
-Yeah. -Yeah. It goes...
嗨  你是在找我嗎
Hello, is it me you're looking for?
伙計們   他們在里面多久了
Guys, how long have they been in there?
-三小時了  -三小時
- About three hours. - Three hours.
三小時
Three hours?
在里頭三小時了  沒出來嗎
They've been in there for three hours? They haven't come out at all?
都沒人出來尿尿或其他什么的嗎
No one came out to take a leak, nothing?
一個也沒
- No.  - Nope.
我站這兒才一會兒就已經感覺不對了
I've been here for three seconds and that sounds odd to me.
我就像獵鷹般的盯著他們
I've been watching that tent like a hawk.
是嗎  我怎么看到你們只是坐這兒吃意大利肉汁燴飯
Really? lt looks like you're eating some risotto and sitting on your ass.
我不知道了  我想來點湯
I don't know. I wanted the soup.
-我吃的不是意大利肉汁燴飯  -真不是
- I wasn't eating risotto. I had... -It's not risotto.
伙計們
Yeah, boys.
他想挑事呀
Yeah, he wants to fight, doesn't he?
靠這也太爽了  還給我們找了跳脫衣舞的妞呀
Damn, this is awesome. They got us a stripper, too.
你眼神就像我們當兵的一樣性感  比如說我
You got that hot enlisted look. Me likey.
在我關你們禁閉之前  我想知道  他們哪去了
Before l throw you in the stockade, where are they?
沒跟我們說哦  上尉
They didn't tell us... Captain.
只給了我們一箱啤酒和每人五十塊
They just gave us a case of beer and 50 bucks apiece.
給我的是一百
I got a hundred.
給你的是一百塊呀
Oh, did you get a hundred?
這假發是不是歸咱們了
You think we get to keep the hair?
策劃  行動  部署
Staging, movement, action plan.
你們有得讀了
There's a nice read for you.
太給力了  漢尼拔  要的就是這個
Hell, yeah, Hannibal. This is it right here.
讓人難以置信
This is bat-shit insane.
-完美  -頭兒  太瘋狂了
- It's perfect.  - This is beyond nuts, boss.
習慣就好
It gets better.
怪頭  你去找一塊和你塊頭差不多大的金屬做滑板
B.A., you'll need a piece of contoured metal to make a skid plate.
快走  傻瓜
Let's go, fool.
默多克  去弄塊車用電池
Murdock, we'll need a car battery, too.
看看"黑森林"那群傻帽那邊有不
See if the boys at Black Forest can help us out.
我們還需要記者證
Press credentials, we need them.
到媒體中心的帳篷里去找找
Hit the media tent and see what's lying around.
抱歉  伙計  我看你
Sorry, my friend, l see you've put
剛把南非電視臺的話筒放下邊了
the South African microphone at the bottom.
你不能總讓CNN高高在上
You can't always put the CNN on top.
當兵的  這兒有兩個話筒  我不清楚是
Private, there are two mics. I don't know if there is something...
早先我曾是個帥小伙
I was a moving man in my younger days
默多克  我們得弄臺新聞攝影機
Murdock, we need a news camera.
就看你的了
See what you can do.
抱歉  抱歉
All right, sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
你好  我
Hello. I'm...
我愛上你了
I'm in love with you.
聽著  我們正在做預備性會談
Listen, we're doing a preliminary poll of...
是關于那個什么  對了  撤軍
What are we talking about? Of the pull-out.
還需要氣囊  越多越好
We're gonna need airbags, lots of them.
-你是哪個部門的  -法國世界報
- What bureau are you with, darling?  - Le Monde.
你是法國人
Are you French?
你好  我是帕克爾將軍  我需要
Hello, this is General Parker. I need...
找你的
Okay. It's for you.
要進行空襲  你自己去和上頭說
Hey, fool, you need to call an air strike on yourself.
-我們這沒問題了  老兄  再會  -不  我們得回去
- We're good, mate. I'll meet you.  - No, I think we need to get going now.
你給我聽清楚了
You need to understand what I'm telling you right now.
怪頭  弄塊磁鐵
B.A., we're gonna need a magnet.
要磁力夠強的
A powerful one.
看過藍人樂隊的演出嗎
You ever seen Blue Man Group?
其他的交給我
I'll pick up the rest.
我想冒次險
I'm just gonna go for it.
你愿意付出一切  換取這個機會嗎
What would you give for one chance
那就是回來大聲告訴我們的敵人
to come back here and tell our enemies
他們也許能奪走我們的生命
that they may take our lives,
卻永遠奪不走我們的自由
but they'll never take our freedom!
惡搞《勇敢的心》
準備好進城了嗎
Ready to go downtown?
祝君好運
Good luck.
-謝謝  -讓他們見鬼去吧
- Thank you.  - Give 'em hell.
莫里森將軍  漢尼拔·史密斯在他媽哪兒呀
General Morrison, where the hell is Hannibal Smith?
上尉   和首長說話要禮貌
Captain, you would do well to revise your tone and readdress me.
將軍  我奉命可以隨時取代你
General, I have authority under DClS that supersedes your command,
為免難堪  我最后再問你一次
so last time, before this becomes embarrassing for the both of us,
漢尼拔在哪兒
where is Hannibal Smith?
你先出去下  將軍
Would you excuse us, General?
上尉  我從軍快四十年了
Captain, in nearly 40 years of being in this army,
已經不是剛當兵時的火爆脾氣了
I have learned to control my temper
特別是對待下屬時我更會和和氣氣
and my voice when in the presence of a subordinate officer
現在到底是誰他媽的說話這么不客氣
who, for at least the time being, seems to have lost her goddamn mind.
我理解是
Now, it is my understanding
你有事要問我  對吧
that you have a question for me. ls that correct?
是的
You are correct, sir.
你要記住  你還是一名美國軍官
Then when you are prepared to remember that you are still an officer
盡管你現在沒穿著軍裝
in the United States Army, in spite of your civilian attire,
當兵的就要有當兵的樣
and are ready to present that question in a military fashion,
這樣我們才能談的下去
then perhaps we could get somewhere with this discussion.
如果你派遣天龍特攻隊去了巴格達
lf you have sent an Alpha Team into Baghdad for any reason whatsoever,
就已經違抗了國防部的命令
that is a direct violation of a DoD order.
既然你都這么說了
Well, and as much as you have this kind of knowledge,
還問我作甚
I can't help wondering why it is that you need to ask anything of me.
我就當你是承認了
I will take that as your confirmation, sir.
他們三小時后出發
They go mobile in three hours.
在鑄幣廠里將模板和十多億美元
The plates and over a billion dollars
裝在一輛拖車后面
will be loaded into the back of a semi at the mint.
然后行駛7.4公里到達這座橋
They're overland for exactly 4.6 miles before they reach the bridge.
這是我們的機會  但轉瞬即逝
That's our window, and it closes fast.
一有任何風吹草動  他們都會開大火力
These guys will go weapons hot at the first whisper of trouble.
小白  你得進入酒店地下
Face, your point of entry is under the hotel.
酒店上面肯定擠滿了外國記者和私人保鏢
It'll be packed with foreign press and private security.
怪頭  你帶著計時器等在這條巷子里
B.A., you're in this alleyway on a stopwatch.
車起碼要是雙氣缸引擎
Make sure the bike has V-tins or better.
我弄了輛比那強百倍的
I got something a whole lot better than that.
我干什么呀  頭兒
What about me, boss man?
我有架小型直升機
I had a little helicopter here someplace.
能不能空翻  或是空中熄火
You got some barrel rolls? Some mid-air stalls?
我等不及下一次瀕死體驗了
I'm looking for my next near-death experience.
你這次是支援行動  上尉
Only air support this time, Captain,
下次會讓你大干一場  我保證
but I'll get you in on the next one. I promise.
怪頭  你六點半準時出發
B.A., I need you to pop that clutch at 0630.
我嗎
Is that me?
我都忘了  我在伊拉克的下水道里  太謝謝了  頭兒
Oh, no, l forgot. I'm in an lraqi sewer. Thanks, boss!
時間就是一切  小白
Timing is everything, Face.
關鍵要一擊即中
This is all about the bull's-eyes.
誰說不是
Why not?
在拖車下面  你得把跟在后面的卡車干掉
From under the semi, you'll take out the truck directly behind you.
然后會有人沖著你過來  小白
Now, these guys are gonna be onto you, Face.
怪頭  這時就該你上場了
B.A., that's your cue for throttle.
穿越前先看清兩旁的路
Be sure to look both ways before crossing.
還有別忘了給車加滿油
And have a nice full tank of gas.
車上會有重兵把守  怪頭
You'll have multiple hostiles on board, B.A.
把他們統統解決掉
Escort them from the premises.
要是有人從后面偷襲  別擔心  有我呢
If any stragglers sneak up behind, don't worry, l got your back.
抓住你了  小子
Gotcha, kid.
好樣的
Attaboy.
聽起來不錯  但我們要怎么離開巴格達呢
That's all fine in theory, but I still don't see how we get out of Baghdad.
我心中有數
I do.
怪頭  右轉
B.A.! Hang a right!
好的  抓緊
All right! Hang on!
-小心  -低頭
- Watch out! Watch out!   - Heads down!
干得漂亮  怪頭
Oh! Nice one, B.A. !
小白  裝上氣囊
Face, get the airbags!
得保證一會兒不會脫落
Gotta make sure this thing stays locked for later!
完美
Beautiful!
一  二  三
One, two, three.
頭兒  氣囊是為了防撞擊的吧
Hey, boss, airbags do deploy on impact, right?
怪頭  到集裝箱里去
B.A., get in the container.
注意后方
Contact, rear!
靠
Shit!
我就覺得這部分最不靠譜
See, this is the part of the plan l don't trust!
別擔心  小白  繩子很牢
Don't worry, Face! The rope will hold!
我擔心會被釘在集裝箱上
If l was worried, l'd be nailing myself to the container right now!
抓住了  弟兄們
Hang on, boys!
老子來也  統統給我轟成渣吧
Bam! Come on! l smoked you!
你們看到下面的情況了沒
You boys see that down there?
那傻蛋來干什么
Murdock? What is that fool doing here?
讓我出去  我不是開玩笑
Don't lock me in here. l ain't playing with y'all!
頭兒  你有沒有在游戲廳玩過
Hey, boss, you ever play that game at the fun fair
用爪子抓玩具的游戲
where you try to pick up a stuffed animal with the claw?
這感覺太像啦
This is a lot like that.
就是這樣
That's it!
你們鎖上了是么
Did you lock this?
你們鎖上了是么  你們竟然我把鎖住了
You locked it, didn't you?
漢尼拔  快開門呀  伙計
Hannibal, open this door right now, man!
你是在把這車廂往哪兒掛嗎
What the... Are you hooking this thing?
-是往直升機上掛嗎  -掛好了
- You hooking this up to a helicopter?   - I got you.
到底他媽怎么回事  別這么瘋狂
What the hell's going on?   You ain't that crazy!
別他媽告我現在我在天上  看我怎么弄死你們
Tell me we ain't flying! I'm gonna kill you, fool!
-頭兒  那是博斯克嗎  -快放我出去
- Boss, is that Bosco?  - Get me out of here!
-糟了  -快放我出去
- That's not good.  - Let me out of here!
這下糟了  他不高興了
That's not good. He is not happy.
林奇特工  我臨時從
Agent Lynch, I'm patching surveillance
將軍賬營中打給你
from the General's tent to you now.
長官  現在有架可傾斜旋翼的V22型飛機
Sir, l have an inbound V-22 tilt-rotor
從西北方向接近
on approach from the northwest.
是友非敵  奉將軍之命在此降落
Identified friendly. Landing under the General's orders.
是天龍特攻隊撤退至此  不是敵人
Alpha Delta Alpha, stand down. Checked, friendly.
喀布爾  阿富汗
是我們的人  在臨時著陸區的D區
Those are our boys. D-block perimeter around LZ
攜帶重要物品降落
for essential cargo touchdown.
老羅  大獲全勝
Russ, we are in the net.
收到  我五分鐘后到
Copy that. l will be there in five.
用一大瓶尊尼獲加藍方為你們接風
I've got a big bottle of Blue Label waiting.
一瓶哪夠  最起碼一箱才行  吝嗇鬼
A bottle? Make it a case, Scrooge.
一會兒見
See you in a few.
誰去放他出來
Who's gonna let him out?
-你去  -你去
- You!  - You!
你們都小心著點  等我出去搞死你們
What you don't realize is, now l gotta kill all of y'all!
丫的搞死你們  先滅漢尼拔  然后是默多克
I'll kill all of y'all! Hannibal first, then Murdock!
-頭兒  -最后是小白
- Boss man.  - I'm gonna save Face for last!
-讓我試試  -去吧
- Let me try something.  - Go for it.
真是詭異  我覺得他比那任務還可怕
ls it weird that I'm more scared now than what we just did?
博斯克  我是默多克
Bosco, it's Murdock.
默多克  快開門
Murdock, open this door!
乖  我給你做你愛吃的椰奶咖喱橄欖沙司喲
I'll make you some of that coconut-curry tapenade that you love.
這招估計管用
That might work.
有吐司嗎
With toast points?
當然有吐司  不然
Hell, yeah, with toast points. What, you're gonna have that
要抹在土豆餅上吃嗎
with plain old chips?
-你玩兒我  -猛虎出柵嘍
- Damn! You tricked me.  - There he is.
-出來嘍  -我討厭這樣
- There he is!  - I hate that!
-得了  -離我遠點  伙計
- Come on!  - Get away from me, man!
要不是寡不敵眾我真想揍扁你們
The only reason l don't kick y'all asses is 'cause you all outrank me.
你搞明白點  我討厭在天上飛
You should know better! You know l hate flying!
我滿身是汗  臭氣熏天
I'm wet! I stink!
我還一毛錢都花不了
And l can't spend none of that money!
-用錢買不來幸福  -去你丫的
- Money can't buy happiness.  - Damn, man!
默多克  今晚你來做飯  穿上你的小花圍裙
Hey, Murdock, you cooking tonight. You better get your apron on.
我就愛計劃圓滿的那一刻
I love it when a plan comes together.
-漢尼拔  誰在里面  -是將軍嗎
- Hannibal, who was that?  - General?
-里面是將軍嗎  -老羅
- ls that the General?  - Russ.
-到這兒來  -將軍
- Get there. Get in there.  -  General!
-老羅  -將軍
- Russ!  - General!
將軍
General!
天哪
Jesus Christ.
帕克
Pike.
注意后方
Contact rear!
過去
Get in there!
快過去
Get there, get there!
經過商議  我們決定將你
After conferring, we've decided to demote you
降級到中尉
to the rank of First Lieutenant.
索薩中尉  雖不是你的過失
Lieutenant Sosa, it's nothing personal,
但你卻沒能弄回模板
but you lost those plates.
那便是你的責任
Those were your responsibility.
你就慶幸吧
Consider yourself lucky.
其他人要為此去蹲監獄
Others are going to prison over this.
您好  麥克雷迪檢察官
Good day, Director McCready.
中尉  你可以走了
Lieutenant, you're dismissed.
史密斯上校  本庭無法證實
Colonel Smith, this court has been unable to recover
你執行的那項任務是遵從
any direct order from General Morrison for you to conduct the mission
莫里森將軍的命令
for which you're being tried.
法官大人  這是秘密行動
Your Honor, this was a covert operation
并無官方命令
and no official orders were given.
但唯一能證明此項行動合法性的人
So the one individual who can verify
已經去世了  對吧  上校
the legitimacy of this operation is deceased. Is that correct, Colonel?
不對  法官大人  不是去世
No, Your Honor, not deceased.
羅素·莫里森將軍
美國陸軍
莫里森將軍是被謀殺的
General Morrison was murdered.
上校  像你們這種不守軍規的人
Colonel, I've been around a long time.
我見的多了
I've seen units like yours. They're outlaws.
就是你們這種人
Units like that pose a direct threat
對我軍的軍威軍紀造成了巨大威脅
to the fabric and fundamentals of our military.
法官大人  為何"黑森林"沒有被問責
Your Honors, why hasn't Black Forest been brought to trial?
黑森林及其成員不在我們的管轄范圍內
Black Forest and its personnel are not subject to military jurisdiction.
你的計劃呢  頭兒
Where's the plan, boss? Where is it?
逃跑計劃呢  我沒看到呢
Where's the escape hatch? Because l don't see it.
-這項任務還沒結束  中尉  -什么任務
- This mission isn't over, Lieutenant.  - What mission?
找到帕克和模板  就能洗清罪名
I clear our names. We find Pike and the plates.
不惜一切代價
No matter what.
法官大人  這些人只是依令辦事
Your Honors, these men were acting under my command.
所有處罰都應由我一人承擔
Any judgment should be levied against me, and me alone.
并非如此  長官
Absolutely not, sir.
我們都是自愿參與此行動
We were all participating in this operation willingly.
我不贊成個人頂責
I don't wanna be tried separately.
我也拒絕個人頂責  長官
I refuse to be tried separately, sir.
根據軍事審判統一法典
In accordance with the Uniform Code of Military Justice,
本庭判決A小隊  即天龍特攻隊
this court is rendering guilty verdicts
所有成員罪名成立
for each member of this Alpha Unit, or A-Team,
并委托監獄對你們分開進行最嚴密監禁
and mandating incarceration in separate maximum-security facilities
在未來十年內
for a period of up to 10 years.
撤銷你們的軍銜
You're all hereby stripped of formal rank
并開除軍籍  永不錄用
and dishonorably discharged.
簡直是放屁
This is bullshit, man.
現在休庭
This session is adjourned.
可恥
Disgraceful.
-別碰我  -上尉  退下
- Do not touch me, okay?  - Captain, stand down.
安靜
Order! Order!
絕對的誣陷
Absolute disgrace!
你高興了吧  查瑞莎
You happy? Are you happy, Charissa?
上校  管好你的人
Colonel, control your men!
-把你的手拿開  -這是誣陷
- Get your hands off me!  - This is a disgrace!
六個月后
軍 事 監 獄
科羅拉多
卡森要塞
好久不見  林奇先生
Well, hello, Mr. Lynch. Long time.
在這么多攝像頭下
You look very relaxed, Lynch.
你還能這樣放松
A lot of cameras in here.
確實挺多
Yeah, there are.
但現在它們都有些技術故障
Yeah, well, they seem to be having some technical issues at the moment.
看來錄像里是找不到我了
May not show up till playback.
漢尼拔  能這么稱呼你嗎
Hannibal. Can l call you Hannibal?
不能再叫你上校了
I can't call you Colonel anymore.
我等了
Six months.
你六個月  等著你把這兒炸飛
Been waiting for you to bust out of here
再召回那幫小兄弟
and round up the rest of the Backstreet Boys
帶我去找模板
and lead me to those plates.
但六個月卻毫無音訊
Six months and not a peep.
所有人都以為你們是和帕克一伙兒的
Everybody thought you and your team were working with Pike.
除了你
Mmm. Everybody except you.
帕克謀殺了莫里森  設計陷害我們  偷走了模板
Pike murdered Morrison. Set me and my boys up and stole those plates.
我知道他在哪兒
And I know where he is.
沒人知道他在哪兒
Nobody knows where he is.
這有一張他被拍到的照片
It's a single image of him.
一個月前在歐洲的某處
Taken about a month ago, somewhere in Europe.
大概是監控攝像頭的抓拍
We think it's a grab from a CCTV camera.
是德國的法蘭克福
Frankfurt, Germany.
你怎么知道
How did you get that in here?
我需要的只是時間  林奇
Time, Lynch.
1分鐘我就能做到這樣
Give me a minute and I'm good.
給1小時我會更出色
If I've got an hour, I'm great.
要是給我半年時間  我就無敵了
You give me six months, I'm unbeatable.
帕克我認識
I know Pike.
那個阿拉伯人是誰
Who's the Arab?
不知道
We don't know.
我們覺得他是"深黑"  整個事件的幕后黑手
We think he's the deep, dark, hidden hand in this whole thing.
或是經紀人  或是買主
Maybe a broker, maybe a buyer.
林奇  我們有共同的敵人  而你卻只有一個選擇
Lynch, we have common enemies and you have limited choices.
我的隊伍是你奪回模板的最好選擇
My team is still your best shot at getting those plates back.
這我得想一想
I wouldn't be so sure.
那你干嗎大老遠跑到這兒來
Then why did you make the long drive out here?
你和中情局的伙計們正等著你的決定
You and your boys at Langley want your own private printing press.
行不行就取決于你的愛國心了
That's about as deep as your patriotism goes.
那你需要我如何協助
So, what would you need from me?
我答應過隊員們會為他們洗清罪名
I swore to my team that I would clear our names.
你們都該明白名譽的重要性
You of all people must understand the value of a name.
聽著
Now, listen.
我要求復職與洗清罪名
I want full reinstatement and clean records
我和我的隊員們
for myself and my team.
我無法把你弄出去
I can't get you out of here.
至少合法的途徑上不行
Not legally, at least.
這是中情局的拿手菜
This is something the boys at Langley do very, very well.
浸5毫升河豚毒素的古巴雪茄
劑量一定要準確
Make sure the dosage is right.
準確的意思就是毫厘不差
And when I say right, I mean perfect.
我的幸福鳥呀她還沒來到
Don't seem like happiness will come along
古巴貨 可惜了
Cuban. What a shame.
大家都往我床上丟石塊
Everybody's throwing rocks in my bed
生活停滯不前
Just can't seem to get ahead in life
火葬室
為啥我就搞不定
Ooh, nothing I do ever turn out right
"戰神"  約翰·史密斯  被捕后死于心臟病
為啥沒人來幫幫我
Won't somebody help me, please?
我已寂寞很久了
'Cause I've been lonely for so long
我的幸福鳥呀她還沒來到
Don't seem like happiness will come along
我已寂寞
I've been lonely...
休想在我的
You are not permitted
道場撒野
in my dojo!
看來  撒旦顯靈了
So, Satan walks into this bar...
等等  這都什么  泳池
Wait a minute. What's this, a lap pool?
蒸汽房
A dry steam room?
是啊  還要用很久呢
Yeah, it'll go a long way with the boys.
你到底怎么弄來的
How in the hell do you pull this off?
這不在于和誰關系好  鮑勃  而在于你們關系有多好
It's not who you know, Bob, it's how you know them.
聯邦營地監獄
彭薩科拉
弗羅里達
你兒子從阿富汗回來了嗎
Oh! Did your boy get back from Afghanistan?
對  多虧回來了  我和孩他媽都高興的不得了
Yeah. Thanks for getting him home. His mother and l are real grateful.
上尉
Captain.
你忘東西在我床上了
You left something on the bed.
-你應該藏起來  -藏起來多浪費
- Could have hid those.  - Why would I want to do that?
太銷魂了  八點見
Drive me crazy. I'll see you at 8:00.
-你還要建什么  -泳池和蒸汽房已經有了
-And now you want to build...  -A lap pool and a dry steam.
對了  還要一個日光浴場所
Overlooking a sundeck.
謝謝你的靴子
Hey, LT, thanks for the boots.
客氣啥  我的榮幸  寶貝兒
Ah! Come on. It's my pleasure, baby!
漂亮
Beautiful.
聽著  我知道這對身體有好處
Listen, now l know this is good for the body,
但怎樣保護臉不被曬傷
but how do you protect the face?
小子  你的臉再黑也很帥
You don't mess with it, kid.
呵呵
Gotcha.
-謝謝請我做日光浴  -不客氣
- Thanks for the tan. - You got it.
史密斯越獄了  中尉
Smith has escaped, Lieutenant.
我去抓他回來
Let me go after him.
史密斯他們和布拉德·帕克的黑森林勾結
Smith and his team were working with Brock Pike and Black Forest.
找到他們就能找回模板  長官
I can get those plates back for you, sir.
相信我
You know I can.
哼哼哈嘿
Holla what? Holla who?
哼哼哈
Holla me.
放我出去
Hey! Let me out! Hey, hey! Hey!
我當時就看到他站在那兒  我都傻了  我還以為是鬼
I see him standing there, and I was like, "What?"
他全身烏黑  等我醒來   臉上還很麻木
And then it turned black and I woke up, and my face was numb,
我就
and l just...
你就把他的腳印都用拖把擦了
And you mopped up the footprints that led out,
連你的實驗大褂丟了也沒發覺
ignored the fact that your lab coat,
還有通行證  車鑰匙和你的車
pass card, car keys and car were missing.
胖得好像吞了史密斯在肚中
Looks like he ate Smith.
吉伯特  你或者蓄意
Gilbert, you've either deliberately
與一名聯邦罪犯策劃越獄
aided and abetted a federal fugitive's escape,
或者就是你笨得可以
or you're the single dumbest human being I've ever come into contact with.
-你聞到了嗎   -啥也別說
- You smell that?   - Don't talk about it.
你想知道為啥我要傾著身子嗎
Would you like to know which way I'm leaning?
前鋒的職業病
Forward.
每小時給這家伙做一次尿檢
I would test this man's urine, on the hour.
距離我的假釋聽證會就差一周啊
I was a week away from my parole hearing.
你曬得還真黑啊
You are really tan.
跟你說過了這任務還沒完
Told you the mission wasn't over.
我要重組天龍特攻隊
I'm putting the team back together.
天龍特攻隊不能沒有你  小白
I need you, Face. I can't do this without you.
獄長  為啥有人可以不經你同意去探望史密斯
Warden, how did Smith arrange a personal visit without your consent
你也沒簽字通過呀  這咋就發生了
or your signature? How does that happen?
這該死的家伙怎么辦到的
How the hell did this guy do that?
封鎖起來  誰都不許進去
Seal that up, nobody goes in there.
沒有探監那天的登記記錄
Log-in pages from the day in question have been removed.
-意料之中  -被撕掉了
- Why does that not surprise me?  - Torn out.
雪茄藏在那本書的書脊里
The cigar was in the spine of that book.
-真精密  這書不錯  -不錯
- Subtle. It's a good book.  - Right.
這是全方位監視犯人的攝像錄像
This is surveillance from all around the prison, right?
而屏幕上出現的扭曲是信號干擾
What you're watching is a signal jammer.
每當他路過這些探頭時
Every time he walks through one of these things,
一拍到他的攝像頭都會受到信號干擾
we get massive interference. He waltzes in here and waltzes out.
沒人知道他是誰
Nobody knows who he is.
天呀
God.
哦  這就是那根幫助史密斯上校越獄的雪茄
Yes. The cigar that Colonel Smith broke out of prison with.
-知道比這更不可思議的是什么嗎   -是什么
- Yeah. Wanna hear the crazy part?  - Yes.
實驗檢測到這里面含有足以致命劑量的河豚毒素
Lab reports show lethal amounts of, wait for it, tetrodotoxin.
河豚毒素   那是什么
Tetrodotoxin? What is that?
-可以瀕死的藥物  -能讓人成為睡美人的玩意
-The near-death drug. -Yes, that sleeping beauty thing.
你知道什么人會用這玩意嗎
Yeah. And you know who likes to use that, right?
-誰  -名字都叫林某某的那些人
-Who? -Our friends at Langley.
這是他們的拿手好戲
It's one of their favorites.
你覺得是中情局的人來找的史密斯嗎
Come on, do you really think that the CIA came to the prison to visit Smith?
雖然有些離譜  但我覺得是中情局幫他越獄的
This sounds kind of crazy, but l think the CIA broke him out.
誰幫的忙
Who put us on?
就是在巴格達的那個人  中情局的林奇
The same guy that put us on in Baghdad. Lynch, CIA.
為了什么  洗清罪名嗎  還是復職
What are we talking about? Clean records? Reinstatements?
都是
All of the above.
那帕克呢  還有模板
What about Pike and the plates?
要他們付出代價
Payback.
他們在交換什么  在做什么
What are they exchanging?  What is that?
他就是這樣進來的嗎
Is that how he got this in here?
找找兩張圖中的不圖之處
One of these things is not like the other.
這種游戲我可不在行
I suck at these games.
模板從哪座樓里帶出來的  模板上倒映的是什么
Where's this plate from? What is that plate?
字母F  德國法蘭克福
It's an "F." Frankfurt, Germany.
哦  德國法蘭克福
Oh, Frankfurt, Germany.
史密斯在向我們暗示什么  這不會是巧合
Smith is talking to us. This is not accidental.
這家伙總是胸有成竹
With this guy, there's a plan and two to back it up.
你不是指什么因果報應吧
l take it you didn't get religion inside.
不  是復仇
No. l got revenge.
很好
Good.
我認識幾個人  剛好也有這念頭
I know a couple of guys that'll feel the exact same way.
正合我意
I'm counting on it.
塔霍湖
加拿大
索伯監獄轉監車
《寬容與憐憫  救贖之路》
緊急狀況
馬上出來
緊急狀況  馬上出來
Emergency exit now.
漢尼拔
Hannibal.
緊急出口
拜庫斯  別跑
Baracus, don't do it!
他去哪兒  他要干嘛
Where he going? What's he doing, man?
拜庫斯  真他媽見鬼
Baracus! God damn it!
我是索薩
Sosa.
中尉  派克也越獄了
Lieutenant, Peck's already gone.
什么
What?
還剩拜庫斯和默多克了  著手處理這件事  中尉
Baracus and Murdock are left. Handle it, Lieutenant.
好的
Right. Okay.
我不想再出這種丟臉的事了
I don't want to be embarrassed like this again. Do you?
好  別  別   我們馬上就開始部署人員進行抓捕
Okay. No, no, no, no. We're gonna catch and deploy from here.
派克越獄了
Peck escaped.
-靠  你覺得與史密斯有關嗎  -顯然啊
-Oh, hell. You think Smith is involved?  -Definitely.
立刻準備他們的照片  任何可以立馬識別出他們的
Get graphics on him and Smith. Anything that'll ID them instantly.
默多克被關在曼海姆精神病醫院
I know they got Murdock in a psych ward in Mannheim.
怪頭那家伙又他媽的在哪兒
Right. Okay. Where the hell is B.A. Baracus?
你怎么知道那個門
How did you know that once that door was extracted
-掉下來后能支撐他的體重  -我想嘛
- that it would take his weight?  - l just did. He's...
-他大概有102 104公斤吧  -104公斤
- You know, he's what, 225, 230 pounds?  - 230. Yeah.
你記得我們七年前在委內瑞拉的那次任務嗎
Remember the gag we did in Venezuela seven years ago?
委內瑞拉  記得
Venezuela. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
但那人個子很小
But that was a midget.
我考慮到了
Yeah, I wouldn't go for that.
-嘿  大塊頭  他來了  -回來了
- Hey, big guy. There he is.  - Yeah! He's back.
-回來真好  -得勁呀
- Yeah, it's good to be back.  - Come on.
-回來真好  伙計  -好伙計
- It's good to be back.  - My man.
-見到你真高興  兄弟  -我們也是
- It's good to see you, bud.  - You, too, bro. You, too.
-謝謝  -你氣色不錯
- Thanks.  - You look well.
再見到你們真高興
It's good to see you guys.
-怎么  -你的莫霍克發型呢
- What?  - Where's the Mohawk?
怎么  不喜歡我的新發型嗎
What, you don't like my new do, man?
啥  不是給你準備推子推頭了嗎  我以為
Do I like it? Well, we got you the clippers. I thought...
我這不是用了嘛
Yeah, I used them.
怎么了  大塊頭
Hey. What's up, big guy?
跟我們講講
Come on, you can speak to us.
伙計們
Guys...
我不能再殺人了
I can't kill anybody.
-什么意思  -我發過誓
- What do you mean?  - I've taken a vow.
-什么誓  -遠離暴力
- Vow?  - Of non-violence.
我仍會跟你們合作
I'll still do anything for you guys, you know that.
但我不會殺人
But I just can't kill, man.
雖然舊習難改
Old habits may die hard,
但終將改過
but they still gotta die.
小時候大家都說
When l was a kid, all you heard in the hood was,
博斯克是個大壞蛋  嗜殺如狂
"Bosco's a badass, out collecting scalps."
所以我留莫霍克頭
That's where the Mohawk came from.
于是我一直在戰斗
Was always at war.
這就是戰士的宿命
And that's what warriors are for.
漢尼拔  伙計  我不想要這種生活
Hannibal, man. I don't miss that life.
我會幫忙把默多克弄出來  扭轉我們的的不公待遇
I'll help you get Murdock, and right that wrong,
-但不能殺人  -帕克也不殺嗎
- but I can't kill.  - Even Pike?
即使殺掉他能洗清你的罪名
Even if killing him would clear your name?
我現在只想對得起自己的良心
My conscience is the only thing l need clear.
那么  那個小瘋子大蠢蛋在哪兒
Now, where's that crazy-ass fool?
情感轉移
Transference.
情感康復
Healing feelings.
不能把感情全堆在心里
You can't warehouse these things, you know?
你只有發泄出來才會有所好轉
You have to express to progress.
要為你的情感大廈添磚加瓦
We gotta empower your emotional tower
你要珍惜自己也要學會接受別人的愛
and send out a wavelength of self-love and acceptance.
謝謝
Thank you.
陸軍精神病醫院
德國曼海姆
就緒
Clear.
好像不起啥作用  這沒法展開相應的治療呀
He seems completely impervious to it. It's impossible to develop a base reading.
加大電壓了嗎
Have you increased the voltage?
每回都加
Every single session, yes.
-情感康復  寶貝  -結果呢
- Healing feelings, baby.  - And?
就這點威力嗎  來吧
Is that all you got? Here we go.
就緒
Clear.
我覺得好像感覺到了什么
Yeah, I think I might have felt something there.
我不會入睡的
Oh, no, I won't sleep.
小霍華德
Howard Little.
安娜貝拉·史密斯寄給你的包裹
You have a package here from an Annabelle Smith.
我不認識這人
I don't know any Annabelle Smith.
你認識的  豪伊
Sure you do, Howie.
你肯定認識呀   安娜貝拉
Sure you do, baby. Annabelle.
還記得峴港市的那個護士不   紅頭發  雙腿殘疾的那姑娘
Remember the nurse from Da Nang? The redhead, double amputee?
她有架專業級的懸掛式滑翔機  想起沒
Professional hang glider? Yes!
伙計們
Guys.
安娜貝拉
Annabelle.
安娜貝拉   超越了自我  看看
Annabelle. You have outdone yourself. Look at this.
-太真實啦  -真美
- It's so real.  - Beauty.
3D電影
A movie in three dimensions.
準備戰斗  我的士兵
Stand-to, soldier.
-敵軍在逼近西部戰線  -老天呀
- Jerries advancing on the western front.  - Good heavens.
派你去執行一項秘密任務
Got a secret mission for you.
把這些分發給大伙
Take these and distribute them amongst the men.
-遵命  長官  - 不要辜負女王殿下
-Yes, sir. -Don't fail the Queen.
-一定完成任務  -好樣的
- No, sir.  - Great.
遵命
Yes, sir.
看電影  看電影
Movie, movie, movie...
我將授爵于你
l knight you.
你得把頭低下  站起來重做
Sir, you have to put your head down. Stand up and do it again.
電影
Movie, movie...
現在讓我們為女王殿下放聲歌唱   聽我指揮   先別坐下
Now let's sing to the Queen.  When l ask you... Not yet.
-看電影  看電影  -看電影  看電影
- Movie, movie...  - Movie, movie...
你們拿到眼鏡了
You get glasses! You get glasses!
球來了
Ball!
跪下的時候得低下頭
When you kneel, you put your head down straightaway.
抬頭盯著我看是不尊重的  明白嗎
Looking me in the eye is disrespectful. Do you understand?
看電影
Movie, movie...
你正盯著我看  不對
You're looking me in the eye now. That's wrong.
看電影
Movie, movie, movie...
水族先生  你好
Aquaman? Hello.
你們拿到眼鏡了
You get glasses! You get glasses!
起立  3D先生  好好享受電影的樂趣吧
Rise, Sir 3D, and enjoy your motion picture.
-看電影  -看電影
-Movie! Movie! -Movie! Movie!
伙計  我能離開兩小時不
Boy, could l use two hours of not this.
準備好鎮靜劑  再給這幫瘋子要點比薩餅
Pass out the sedatives and order some pizzas for these freaks.
-看電影  -看電影
-Movie, movie... -Movie, movie...
看電影
Movie...
靠
Shit.
有什么需要幫忙嗎
Excuse me, can l help you with something?
有  我們找默多克上尉  他在哪兒
Yes. Captain Murdock, where is he?
-那邊的房間里  -謝謝
- Right through there.  - Thank you.
霹靂教頭
El diablo.
電影
行了  都坐下
Okay. Settle down.
看電影不許說話
No talking during the movie.
前面坐下
Down in front!
看呀  伙計  這是立體的
Look, it's 3D, man!
我看3D的片子有點暈
I'm sick of 3D.
默多克上尉
Captain Murdock.
記得我嗎  在巴格達見過的
You remember me from Baghdad?
簡直是無用功  這是個傻子
Okay, this is pointless. This guy is fried.
所以他才呆在這兒
Yeah, there's a reason why he's in here.
除他以外的所有天龍隊員都已越獄
And his entire team has escaped, except him.
電影
Movie!
注意觀察周圍  不要讓別人靠近他
Take a look around anyway. Let's make sure he's alone.
遵命  女士
Yes, ma'am.
更大的逃亡  惡搞電影《大逃亡》(1963)
親愛滴上尉  您的戰車正侯駕
Oh, Captain, your chariot awaits.
抱歉小的們  先走一步  電影就這么沒啦
Sorry, boys, gotta run! Can't finish the movie.
得讓我看到結尾吧
Do let me know how it ends.
查瑞莎  你藏哪兒呢  別氣皺你那漂亮臉蛋兒  寶貝
Charissa, where are you hiding? Stay beautiful, baby.
你們應該去看看3D電影中子彈橫飛的畫面
You guys should see these bullets in 3D!
追上那車
Get the truck!
他們在朝我們射擊
She's actually shooting at us.
子彈還是3D的呢
You guys should see these bullets in 3D!
-把頭收回來  -像真的被槍打一樣耶
- Murdock, get in here!  - It's like we're actually being shot at!
你再這樣真的會吃槍子  瘋子大蠢蛋
You are getting shot at, you crazy-ass fool!
-馬上停車  -撞飛它
- Stop right there!  - Ram it.
我說停下
Hey! I said halt!
爽  抱歉啦伙計
Damn! Sorry, dude.
他們好像朝飛機跑道去了
lt looks like they're headed for the tarmac.
快出發
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
-先生們  -該死  是漢尼拔·史密斯
- Gentlemen.  - Holy shit, that's Hannibal Smith.
你們有誰是持槍逃跑的聯邦逃犯嗎
Are any of you armed and/or wanted federal fugitives?
-沒有  -但我們都是
- No.  - Well, we're both.
-那么  -我不喜歡這個主意
- Which means...  - This is a bad idea.
這是個壞點子
This is a bad idea.
別這么孩子氣  上飛機去  像個大人一樣
Stop being a baby. You're a grown-ass man. Get on the plane.
-你要劫機嗎  -所以我才加入陸軍
- You're taking the plane?  - And that's why I joined the Army.
男人點兒  快進去  我們要勝利大逃亡了
We gotta finish the escape. Man up and get in there.
你們是最聰明最頂尖的人才  非常感謝  你們可以走了
The best and brightest. Appreciate it, boys. That'll be all.
鑰匙咧  我要鑰匙
Who's got the keys? l just need your keys.
-什么狗屁鑰匙  -開飛機難道不要鑰匙的嗎
- What you talking about keys?  - You don't need no keys for no plane.
-我真的需要鑰匙  -干毛用  真是餿主意
- I do need keys.  - For what? This is a bad idea.
我們剛把這瘋子從精神病院弄出來
We just broke this guy out of a psych ward.
漢尼拔  還是用剛才那些真的飛行員比較靠譜
Hannibal, you let the real pilots go.
-怪頭  放心  沒問題的  -吃一顆
- B.A., relax. You're gonna be fine.  - Take one of these.
這是啥  要把我弄暈嗎  最好是把我弄暈
What is this? Will it knock me out? It better knock me out,
不然暈的就是你
'cause if it don't, I'm gonna knock you out.
博斯克  這些按鈕讓我很迷茫
Bosco, the buttons are confusing me.
-閉嘴  默多克   -拜托了  默多克  快走
- Shut up, Murdock.  - Come on, Murdock. Let's go.
讓我坐這破飛機  算了吧  我還不如去自首
You gonna fly this plane? Forget it. I'll turn myself in.
-這是干啥用的  -快點
- What does this do?  - Come on.
-快點  默多克  -運氣真好
- Come on, Murdock.  - I got lucky.
扶好了  小的們
Hang on, boys.
停
Stop. Stop, stop, stop.
小白  你女朋友耶
Face, your girlfriend is back.
-立刻倒車  -我操他媽的
- Reverse now.  - Son of a bitch!
快點倒車
Move your ass now.
C-1 30型運輸機和梅賽德斯-奔馳的巔峰對決
The C-1 30 versus the Mercedes-Benz.
快起飛  默多克
Lift us off, Murdock.
-再快點   -快點
- How about faster?  - Faster!
我盡力  全速行進了
I'm trying. l got it pinned!
上帝呀
Oh, my God!
接飛行控制中心
Get us to flight control.
女士們  先生們  稍后飛機會稍有顛簸
Ladies and gentlemen, we are expecting slight turbulence.
請在座位上不要離開直到機長
Please remain in your seats until the captain has turned off
解除警報
the "Fasten Seatbelt" sign.
孩子們別擔心  小小顛簸不足恐懼
Don't worry, boys! Turbulence has never brought down a plane!
他媽的那是什么
What the hell is that?
我們被亞音速無人機和導彈鎖定了
But we got inbound subsonic UAVs with missile lock!
它們簡直就是灰機的天敵
And they bring down planes all the time!
他們來了  反導彈裝置發射
Okay, they're coming in. Launching countermeasures!
看到沒  命懸一線刺激吧
Did you see that? That's my diversion!
它們被我滅了
They die on this version.
堅持住  我們轉過去
Hang on! Hang on! Hold on! We're going over.
默多克  你他媽的發什么瘋
Murdock, what the hell are you doing?
想念墨西哥的時候了嗎
You boys remember Mexico?
飛機上的女士們和先生們
Ladies and gentlemen, from the flight deck,
如果你稍微往右邊看一下的話  就會發現
if you look out of the right-hand side of the aircraft, you'll notice
我們的右邊機翼已經著火
that your right wing is on fire.
-請回復  -導彈鎖定待命  長官
- Tango reacquired.   - Missile lock pending, sir.
查瑞莎·索薩中尉  那些人是國防部罪案調查處的重犯
Lieutenant Charissa Sosa, DClS. Major,
不要擊落那架飛機
do not shoot that aircraft down.
緊急出動戰斗機  逼迫他們降落
Scramble fighters and force them to land.
機上有聯邦逃犯
There are federal fugitives on that plane.
他們還偷竊了美軍財物
They've also stolen property from the U.S. Army.
比利  快把輸出掃描從屏幕上去掉
Billy, Billy, l need you to get the nose-cam view up here on my monitor now.
移上去了  長官  好了
It's up, sir. Here it is.
導彈已發射
Missile away, sir.
擊中  成功攔截和摧毀海格力斯號
We have shoot-down. Hercules has been intercepted and destroyed.
我很抱歉  中尉
Sorry, Lieutenant. I'm sorry.
-不是吧   -長官  畢福德號坦克上有降落傘
- l don't believe it.  - We have chute deployment on the Buford.
什么
What?
立刻讓那些無人機停下來
l want these drones taken offline right now!
-離這兒十萬八千里呢  -不管是誰在操控
- They're 3,000 miles away.  - Whoever is running those drones.
給我撥專線電話  不管是誰
Get me a direct line to whoever is running those drones.
快讓那些無機停下來  我該遭批斗了
We gotta get these drones to stand down or I'm gonna be on bitch duty.
我們要活捉那些人
I need to get those men alive!
大家還好嗎
Everybody okay?
他們會覺得我們已經掛了嗎
What are the chances they think we're dead?
可能性不大
Not great.
-我們不在飛機上了吧  -我們真不在那架飛機上了
- Tell me we ain't still on that plane.  - We ain't on that plane.
漢尼拔
Hannibal!
只要在兩萬英尺以下  就死不了吧
If we're under 20,000 feet, we can still breathe, right?
什么兩萬英尺
What are you talking about, 20,000 feet?
-咱們啟動舊火力系統吧  -見鬼
- Let's fire up the old weapons system.  - What the hell, man?
博斯克  這兒悶死了  我要開個窗
Hey, Bosco, a little stuffy. I'm gonna pop a window!
奶奶滴  看誰有能耐  比比吧
What you got, bitches? What you got?
小白  也讓我來耍耍  快點嘛
Let me have a turn, Face! Come on!
-我們怎么會呆在一個墜落的坦克里  -因為飛機爆炸了
- Why are we in a falling tank?  - Because the plane exploded!
什么  啥時候
What... What? When?
就剛才
Recently!
-被收割者擊落了  -什么收割者
- The Reapers shot it down!  - What Reapers?
就是那些現在還窮追不舍的家伙
The same ones that are still trying to kill us!
-漢尼拔  都怪你  -嚴格來講  我們沒在飛了嘛
- l blame you, Hannibal!  - Technically, we're not flying.
廢話  我們是在墜落  混蛋
I know! Because we're falling, fool!
額滴神啊
Oh, Jesus!
2號無人機墜落  我們損失了一架無人機
UAV-2 has splashed down. We just lost one of the drones.
漢尼拔  這下我們慘了
Hannibal, we're in trouble!
伙計們繃緊了
Brace yourselves!
爽翻天了
Awesome!
小白  你操縱主炮
Face, get on to the main gun!
離這八百米的地方有個湖
There's a lake a half-mile away from this position.
-我操他媽的朝誰開火啊  -相信我
- What the hell am l trying to hit?  - Trust me!
-把機槍轉到82度  -開火
- Rotate the turret 82 degrees.  - Fire in the hole!
開火
Fire!
他們是想再射落一架無人機嗎
Are they trying to shoot down that other drone?
不  他們是在駕駛坦克
No. They're trying to fly that tank.
-坦克飛起來咯  -坦克飛不起來  傻逼
- He's flying the tank!  - You can't fly a tank, fool!
-轉到16度  開火  -收到
- Rotate 16 degrees!  - Got it!
開火
Fire!
再轉到34度
Rotate 34 degrees now!
-漢尼拔  -等下
- Hannibal...  - Wait...
開火
Fire!
-控制中心  我們失去了無人機  -確定擊中了嗎
- Control, we have lost...  - Is that a confirmed hit?
右轉正前方  待命
Bring turret full-front and wait!
默多克  關閉艙門
Murdock! Close the hatch!
收到  這樣能行不
Hatch, okay! Did that work? Did that work?
-頭兒  -加把勁呀
- Boss!  - Come on, baby.
-加把勁  -關好艙口沒
- Come on.  - Hatch control?
我還不想這么早死
I'm too young to die!
頭兒  現在都不用瞄準了
Boss! I'm aiming at nothing!
加把勁
Come on.
-先生們  我很榮幸  -加把勁  寶貝兒
- It's been an honor, gentlemen.  - Come on, baby.
最后一次飛行終生難忘啊  上校
The greatest ride is the last ride, Colonel!
-全力開火  -來吧  寶貝
- Fire everything!  - Come on, baby!
我的駕駛技術如何
-上帝保佑呀  上帝顯靈吧  -加把勁
- Get right with God, y'all! This is it!   - Come on!
這對魚類不公平
It's not fair to the fish!
你作弊
You're cheating!
真嘮叨
You with your nagging...
把魚都嚇跑了
...you're chasing them away!
中情局國外辦事處
德國  法蘭克福
好了  辛勤的小蜜蜂
All right. Busy bees, busy bees.
把外套脫了吧  太他媽熱了
Guys, you can take your coats off. Hot as hell in here.
熱得跟蒸桑拿一樣
I'm sweating like a whore in church.
-長官  -什么事
- Sir.  - Yeah?
史密斯一伙人在德國曼海姆劫了一架C1 30運輸機
Smith and his team were engaged in a C-1 30 over Mannheim, Germany,
還擊落了兩架無人機
by two Reaper drones.
不知道是不是數據加密出了故障
I'm not sure if it's an encryption glitch,
但報告里說是被一輛坦克擊落
but it says that they were shot down in a tank.
北美空防司令部想掩蓋為失蹤  但麻煩的是我們
NORAD's calling it an X-out, but there is a conflicting report.
我就知道
I'm sure there is.
一名德國老婦說她看到一輛坦克
I've got a German Hausfrau who says she saw a tank
從沃格斯坦湖里駛出來  坦克里有個人長得很像默多克
drive up and out of Lake Wolgastsee with a guy resembling Murdock...
打擾一下  柏林怎么走
Excuse me, which way to Berlin?
-問她柏林去怎么走  -這不可能
- ...asking for directions to Berlin.  - That's impossible.
史密斯一周內都死了兩次了
Well, this will be the second time Smith has died this week.
對他們來說還有什么不可能的呢
ls that possible?
美國駐歐洲指揮部
德國  斯圖加特
-有什么消息  -看看這個
- What have you got for me?  - Look at this.
我們對史密斯的訪客圖像進行了還原
We just got the unscrambled composite of Smith's visitor in prison,
但沒有查到該人身份
but with no lD on the subject yet.
你好  帥哥
Hello, handsome.
等下  我以前見過他
Wait, I've seen this person before.
我認識這人
l know this guy.
巴格達
Baghdad.
給我洗張清晰的出來  我們開始行動
Get me a clean patch to Langley. We're going fishing.
我都沒聽說過
I barely even heard about it.
我零碎地聽說了些  但這些怎么跟我們扯上了關系
I mean, I heard bits and pieces of it, but how much of that was us?
-我已經  -我在說話呢
- So, l have a...  - l was talking.
-不會和我們牽扯上的  -別說了好嗎
- It's never us.  - Can you stop?
國防部的索薩中尉打來電話
l have a DoD hardline from Lieutenant Sosa.
她找林奇特工
She's looking for Agent Lynch.
林奇特工沒空  一直沒空
He's not available, ever.
巴格達的林奇特工
Agent Lynch, from Baghdad?
在莫里森將軍的帳篷那次
General Morrison's tent?
出去
Out.
為什么雇她
Why do we have her?
因為她超有個性
She's got a fantastic personality. That's why.
請問哪位
With whom am l speaking?
我是索薩上  中尉  你是林奇特工嗎
This is Capt... uh Lieutenant Sosa. ls this Agent Lynch?
不好意思  我不知道你的名字
I'm sorry, I don't have a first name.
我也不知道  有何貴干  中尉
Neither do I. So, what can l do you for, Lieutenant?
我看見一張你在卡森要塞
I'm looking at an image of you
訓練營的照片
from the disciplinary barracks at Fort Carson.
真性感
She's hot.
你在監獄里探訪過前上校漢尼拔·史密斯嗎
Did you visit former Colonel Hannibal Smith in prison?
我不知道你在說什么  前上尉
I don't know what you're talking about, former Captain.
林奇特工  如果是你協助史密斯逃走
Agent Lynch, if you facilitated Smith's escape
并且正在暗中協助和支持他的話
and are currently aiding and abetting him...
那可真是
Ooh. Buddy.
要是換作是你  這么做的話
lf you can make something like that stick,
可就一步登天了啊
your next promotion should be in the five-star range.
如果你還要協助他們搶回模板
And if you're helping to retrieve those engraving plates,
那我就不得不出手阻止你了
I'm going to have to go out of my way to disappoint you.
查出她的電話  電腦和其它輔助設備
I want her phones, her computers, any support packages she operates.
我要掌握一切  我要攔截她的所有情報
I wanna know everything. I want active intercept taps on everything she's got.
從現在開始監視她的一舉一動
l want every move monitored from this moment forward.
她可是國防部的人
You realize she's DoD.
她是天王老子我也不怕  照做
I don't care if she's G-O-D. Do it.
長官  看看這個
Boss, check this out.
這張照片上  帕克是在法蘭克福的孔希斯銀行
We've tracked this photograph of Pike to the K?nigsbank in Frankfurt.
監控錄像記錄了上個月
Our surveillance has him and an unknown Arab
他一直和一個阿拉伯人一起
making regular trips from the train station to the bank
從火車站到銀行去
all over the last month.
-帕克大意了  -要是我們查到了
- Pike's getting sloppy.  - Yeah, but if we're onto him,
史密斯那伙人會不會也盯上了他們
what are the odds that Smith and his team are onto Pike and the Arab, too?
不  不  這是國防部的高度機密信息
No, no, no, this is a direct pull-down from the Pentagon's database.
史密斯他們絕不可能得到這情報
There's absolutely no way Smith and his team could have this stuff.
不要低估他們  他們的情報遠比我們得要多
I think we should assume they have more information than us at all times.
帕克自上個月以來  就一直把模板
Pike has been moving the stolen engraving plates
往法蘭克福的孔希斯銀行大樓運送
to the Konigsbank Tower in Frankfurt over the past month.
明天是最后一批箱子
Tomorrow, the last of the cases containing these plates
之后將轉交給阿拉伯人
will be transferred to the Arab.
這是過去六個月來
This will mark the only time in the last six months
這些模板第一次集中出現
that all of the plates have been in one location.
要奪回它們  這是最好也是唯一的一次機會
It's our best and only shot at getting them back.
他們離開孔希斯銀行大樓  乘坐七點一刻到蘇黎世的火車
They leave the Konigsbank Tower for the 7:15 train to Zurich.
先生們  我們可不能讓他們如愿了
Gentlemen, we're gonna make sure they miss that train.
-小白  -在
- Face?  - Yeah.
去找你的舊愛吧
Time to bring in your former flame.
要是她真如我所料那般犀利
If she's as good as l think,
現在就該去法蘭克福了  為了攔截那些模板
then she'll be on her way to Frankfurt to intercept those plates.
-你為何要關照她  -她是個理想主義者
- Why would you tip her off?  - She's a crusader,
也許我們之后會用得到她
and we're gonna need her teed up at some point.
提高警惕  伙計們
Keep your eyes and ears open, boys.
查瑞莎·索薩
Charissa Sosa...
問題在于
Now the wrinkle.
要是索薩盯上了我們  也就可以推測  林奇也盯上了她
If Sosa's onto us, we can assume that Lynch is onto her.
要是林奇覺得她是個麻煩人物
And if he thinks she stands beteen him and those plates,
他就會毫不猶豫地干掉她
he won't hesitate to kill her.
小白  去火車站
Face, get to the train station.
我是索薩
This is Sosa.
要是林奇威脅到她  你要負責搞定
If there's a threat from Lynch, deal with it.
喂
Hello?
可以開槍  重復一遍  可以開槍
Shoot is green. Say again, shoot is green.
喂
Hello?
不對勁
Something's wrong.
我們成了靶子  快撤  這情況不妙
We're marked, guys. Pull back. I don't like this at all.
記住  別被人看到
See. Don't be seen.
-你好  美人兒  -你真夠膽
- Hello, beautiful.  - You have got some balls.
-居然丟給我個手機  -沒辦法
- You put a drop phone on me?  - l had to, babe.
只有這樣我才能跟你說話  林奇掌握著你所有的通訊線路
It's the only way I could talk to you. Lynch has all your comm lines.
-你都快撤掉你的人  -我會找到你的  小白
- I want you to pull your team now.  - I'm gonna find you, Face.
不要跟她或其他任何人直接接觸
But do not engage her or anyone else directly.
我先找到你再說吧
Not if l find you first.
別  好了  好了
Come on, all right... Okay. Okay.
往 這 兒 看
天啊
Ow! Ow! Jesus!
-你到底想怎么樣  -救你命
- What the hell are you doing?  - Trying to save you!
查瑞莎
Charissa.
你知道我們是無辜的  你心里清楚
Come on, you know we're innocent. You know this.
你在撒謊  就像你在巴格達那樣
You're lying. Like you lied in Baghdad.
我不知道  我對模板的事一無所知
I did not know. l knew nothing about the plates.
當時的確不知道
At that... At that time.
你謊話連篇
You are completely full of shit!
你就別一套一套的了
Will you stop selling yourself on that
當時明明是你騙了我
and avoiding the fact that you lied to me!
-明明是你騙我  -什么時候
- You're the one that misled me.  - When?
-得了  你想翻舊賬嗎  -不錯
- Come on. You wanna go there?  - Yeah, let's go there.
你知道我是玩玩的  你也就想和我玩玩
You heard l was a player and you wanted to play.
但我開始變得認真了  你就慌了
And then l got serious and you freaked!
-我慌了嗎  我才沒有慌  -你慌了
- Oh, l freaked? l did not freak!  - Yes, you did.
你驚慌失措  然后落跑
You panicked and you ran.
想想吧  查瑞莎
Charissa, come on.
我可是聯邦逃犯  你也知道我被通緝
I'm a federal fugitive. You know exactly how wanted I am.
你覺得我干嘛來法蘭克福  來找老情人嗎  才不是
You think I came to Frankfurt to hash out some old heartbreak? No!
我之所以來這兒  因為不是我們干的  我們是被人陷害
I'm here because we didn't do this. I'm here because we were set up.
我相信最終會真相大白  所以我來這里冒險
I'm here because, in the end, the truth is worth the risk.
就算你不信任我  我也相信你
And I believe in you, even if you don't believe in me.
天  我都忘了你原來這么美
God, I forgot how beautiful you are.
收好這部手機
Hold on to that phone.
我的老天
OH MY GOD!
他有槍
HE'S GOT A GUN!
就在那兒  他有槍
RlGHT THERE! HE'S GOT A GUN!
槍
A GUN!
真廢柴
Sucker.
-見鬼  -派克在哪兒
- Oh, shit.  - Where's Peck?
別光是問  快去找他
Excellent question. Find him!
請保持鎮靜  從最近的出口離開
Please stay calm and go to the nearest exit.
孔希斯銀行大樓
德國  法蘭克福
三號通道見
Meet you up on corridor three.
三號報告  現在一切正常
Three to base. We're all clear at this time.
包裹安全后給我確認一下
Give me confirmation as soon as the package is secure.
我們要看到視頻監視畫面
We need a video feed.
好了  開始吧
Okay, let's dance.
各就各位  準備行動
Coming down. Positions, prepare to move.
像平時一樣  跟緊我  先生
As always, stay close to me, sir.
正在關閉第十層
Closing off the 10th floor.
十層的人   我們需要支援
Tenth floor, we need backup.
回來
Get back! Get back!
我什么都看不見
l can't see anything.
頭兒  情況如何
How we doing there, big man?
默多克  接好阿拉伯人
Murdock, here comes the Arab.
這是一個向左邊中場的
And here's a long drive
長傳遠射
hit deep into left center field.
默多克殺了回來  他是背水一戰  竟然接住了
Murdock's back, he's at the wall, and he makes the catch!
我喘不過氣來了
I can't breathe.
這是個圈套
It's a trap!
皮特  我們需要支援
Pete, we need backup!
怪頭  箱子丟了
B.A., I lost the case.
我受到攻擊  準備撤離
I'm taking fire. I'm out of here.
怪頭  快去拿回模板
B.A., get to those plates.
一群聯邦政府人員已經對
Deutsche Federal is responding to explosions and shots fired
-孔希斯大樓的爆炸和槍擊做出了反應  -趕快離開這里
- at the Konigsbank building.  - Get us out of this mess and get us
-趕去大樓那邊  -遵命
- to that building as soon as possible.  - Yes, ma'am.
是你逼我的  拜庫斯
You made me work for this one, Baracus.
沒想到我會這么狼狽
I didn't think l was this out of shape.
真不走運
I am, unfortunately.
其他人呢
Where's the rest of the team, huh?
史密斯  派克  還有那個傻逼飛行員  他叫什么來著
Smith. Peck. That idiot pilot, the asshole. What's his name?
我要把你打得屁股尿流  拜庫斯  看看你有什么能耐
I'm gonna take this one out of your ass, Baracus. Let's see what you got.
來啊  發什么愣  沒力氣了嗎
Come on. What are you doing? What, are you tired?
我不想傷害你  老兄
I'm not gonna hurt you, man.
不  你傷不了我  等著挨揍吧
No, you're not gonna hurt me, I'm gonna hurt you.
-我不想殺了你  伙計  -你不想嗎
- l don't wanna kill you, man.  - You don't wanna kill me?
你根本殺不了我  我要殺了你  拜庫斯
You're not gonna kill me. I'm gonna kill you, Baracus.
我沒在開玩笑  帕克
I'm not playing with you, Pike.
來吧  我有兩把槍  記得吧  我是左撇子
Here we go, because I got two guns. I'm a lefty, remember that, right?
剛剛打斗的時候  槍已經上膛了吧
So, as soon as that hammer goes back, it's on.
我發誓  我做得出來
I swear to God, I'll do it.
你不是懦夫吧
You're not a coward, are you?
是不
Are you?
真難看
Whoopsy.
去你媽的
Damn!
-要搭車嗎  大塊頭  -你救了我一命  老兄
- Need a ride, big fella?  - You're a life-saver, man.
我下不了手
I couldn't shoot him.
讓開  趴下
Get out of the way! Get down! Get down!
這么多條子
Yeah, this is about the right amount of cops.
你真可愛  你應該慶幸周圍都是人
That's cute. You're lucky there are people around.
不  親愛的  你才應該慶幸
No, sweetheart, you're lucky.
你不熱下再吃嗎
You eat that cold?
我不講究
Any way I can get it.
屋頂有處地方漏了
There's a leak in the roof.
好多處都漏了
There's a lot of them.
-他們回來了  -是的
- Is that them?  - I got it.
好吧  我沒偷看過阿拉伯人
All right. Not a peep out of the Arab.
索薩當時在火車站
Sosa was at the train station.
-你見她了嗎  -是的
- You saw her?  - Yeah.
你和她談過了嗎
Did you talk to her?
我別無選擇  好嗎  相信我
I had no choice, okay? Just trust me on that.
信你個頭  一涉及到女人你就頭腦發熱
I trust you to make historically bad decisions
盡出昏招
as far as women are concerned.
你到底是怎么想的
What part of you is thinking at the moment?
林奇的人要殺她  我必須阻止
Lynch's men moved in on her and l had to react.
這不是你派我去的初衷嗎
That's why you wanted me there in the first place...
是去阻止而不是去泡她
To stop them! Not to engage her!
只有先泡上了她  我才能去阻止他們
I couldn't do one without the other.
得了  我很懷疑
Please. Somehow I doubt that.
你干嘛這么生氣  我們找回了模板
Hey. What are you so pissed about? We got the plates.
她也得到了情報
You wanted her teed up. She's teed up.
她知道我們沒偷
She knows we didn't steal them.
她肯定急于查出真正的幕后黑手
She'll be thrilled to find out who did.
什么
What?
你一定知道
You had to know.
你一定知道  如果你留我一條命  這一刻遲早會到來
You had to know if you left me alive, that this was coming.
你怎么會不知道呢
How could you not?
你教會了我一切
You taught me almost everything I know.
漢尼拔  你認識這個人嗎
Hannibal. You know who this is?
我們都認識
We all do.
莫里森
Morrison?
不是吧
Hell, no.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
不知道這算不算祝福  行動順利  朋友
Not so sure that it is a blessing, but good hunting, my friend.
謝謝
Thank you.
你個賤人
You son of a bitch.
莫里森  真天殺的
Morrison? Holy shit.
你不是將軍
You're not a general.
你把他怎么了
How could you do this to him?
你對得起我們嗎
How could you do this to us?
你不配當將軍
You know nothing about leading men.
我就知道  林奇如果協助我逃跑  那你肯定也有參與其中
I knew if Lynch helped me escape, you had to be part of it.
你和帕克利用模板和林奇達成協議
You and Pike were making a play on those plates with Lynch,
但你背叛了他
and you turned on him.
就像你背叛我們一樣
The way you turned on us.
林奇本來就沒把我們算在內
Lynch was never gonna cut us in.
他只是在利用我們
He was gonna use us.
為保險起見他才把你拉進來
He brought you on as insurance.
你就沒想過  這是背叛了你的摯友嗎
He never thought you'd betray your oldest living friend.
我只是先下手為強  漢尼拔  我是個戰士
I just hit first, Hannibal. I'm a fighting man.
你是個騙子  叛徒
You're a liar and a traitor!
別廢話了  殺了我
Then don't draw this out. Kill me.
好主意呀
That's a fantastic idea!
頭兒  讓我來
Bos, let me do this.
小白   我可不殺人
Face, I ain't killing nobody.
你不殺  我殺
You're not, Bosco. I am.
不管他說啥  別殺他  好嗎
No matter what he says, do not kill him, okay?
不想看就別過頭去
You guys don't wanna watch? Just turn your heads.
-我不贊成殺他  -我也很想殺了他
- I'm not gonna be party to it neither.  - I wanna kill the son of a bitch, too,
但他是我們的救命稻草
but he's our ticket out.
他終于不說瘋話了  聽他一回
He knows what he's talking about for once. Listen to him.
-小白  他是我們唯一的證人  -默多克
- Face, he is our only evidence.  - Murdock, Murdock...
-明白不  -我們現在都是他害的
- Do you understand?   - He put us here.
等他給我們做完證再崩了他
You can blow his head off after he testifies, okay?
他把一切都毀了
He's ruined it!
-好好想想你在做什么  小白  -好了
- Think what you're doing, Face.  -  All right.
-如果你不能  -夠了 兄弟們
- If you can't handle it...  - Boys, enough.
夠了  小白
Enough! That's enough, Face.
夠了  退下
Enough! Step down!
大家都出去
Everybody outside
我來
I got him.
-還是讓我干掉他吧  -小白  出去
- I don't want you to have to do it.  - Face, outside.
退下
Stand down, soldier.
小白  馬上
Face. Now!
-真他媽愚蠢  -你沒事吧  伙計
- Fucking stupid.  - You okay, man?
你知道莫里森偽裝成阿拉伯人
You knew Morrison was masquerading as the Arab.
-為什么不告訴我  -我也不能百分之百肯定
- Why not share that?  - I wasn't 100% sure.
只有99%的把握嗎
How about 99%?
你不覺得這很重要嗎
Would you think it was worth mentioning then?
林奇  你到底在想什么
Lynch, what did you think?
你覺得我會當場殺了他嗎
You think I'd just kill him on the spot?
我知道你不會  我相信你
I was certain of it. I still am.
你拿到模板了嗎
Do you have the plates?
當然  不然我會打給你嗎
I wouldn't be calling you if I didn't.
史密斯  歸還模板  殺了莫里斯  你們就能洗清罪名
Smith, return the plates, kill Morrison, and reclaim your lives.
我要白宮  國務院
I want signed and authorized amnesty agreements
和三軍參謀長聯席會議
for myself and for each of my men.
所簽署并授權的赦免令
From the White House, the State Department
給我和我的兄弟們
and the Joint Chiefs of Staff.
你聽到了嗎
You hear me?
再給我點時間
I'm gonna need a little more time.
要多久
How much?
目標時間倒計時
五分鐘
Give me five minutes.
我等著
I'm waiting.
還不明白嗎  漢尼拔
Don't you get it, Hannibal?
我們為他們打仗  流血  犧牲
We fight for them, we bleed for them, we die for them...
他們才不管我們死活
They don't give a rat's ass.
死亡和毀滅
Death and destruction,
對他們來說無足輕重
they're selling it like it was on the goddamn commodities exchange.
你別指責他們   和他們無關
Don't push this off on them. This is not about them.
你所謂的反戰已經造成了數十億美元的損失
Your war protest was stealing billions of dollars!
你到底是誰
Who are you?
我是將軍  你是名上校
I am a general. You are a colonel.
我指揮  你行動
I say, "Jump," and you say, "How high?" End of story.
你該上路了
It is now.
我親眼看到你在阿靈頓的墓碑
l saw your tomb at Arlington.
為國捐軀的軍人均葬于此
你是為國捐軀的英雄
You died a national hero.
死了太便宜你
Death's too easy.
我們再也不想聽什么謊言了
And the last thing we need now is another lie.
別這樣  漢尼拔  你欠我那么多
Don't do this. Hannibal, please. You owe me that much.
是你欠我
You owe me!
你要去告訴世人  我們是無罪的
You're gonna tell them we're innocent.
你欠我的
You owe me.
漢尼拔  你們所為之而戰的東西
Hannibal, it's meaningless.
根本毫無意義
What are you fighting for now, you and those boys?
你們的軍銜和名譽
Your ranks? Your reputations?
都是狗屁
They're shit!
你們就是罪人
You're convicts!
不管有沒有模板   你們都是聯邦逃犯
Plates, no plates, you are federal fugitives,
等他們利用完了你  漢尼拔  照樣把你丟棄
and when they're done with you, Hannibal, they just fucking burn you.
祖魯一號  我是闊劍  準備行動
Zulu one, Zulu one, this is Broadsword, you're clear to engage.
闊劍  這名字你起的嗎
"Broadsword." Did you come up with that?
好酷的名字   闊劍
That's awesome. "Broadsword."
闊劍
"Broadsword."
頭兒  你會那樣做嗎
Boss, could you do that?
對我們
To us?
就像莫里森那樣對我們
What Morrison did?
不  永遠不會
No. Not in a million years.
是啊  但你卻失算了
Yeah, but you didn't see it coming, though.
你什么時候就認出他來了
How long did you know it was him?
你們瘋了嗎
Are you guys crazy?
你本來就是瘋子  但  小白  你在譴責漢尼拔嗎
I know you are, but, Face, are you accusing him?
我寧愿被特警隊亂槍打死也不會背叛你們
I'd rather face a firing squad than betray you boys.
自己人不要吵起來
Don't let this tear us apart.
至少現在不能吵
Not now.
我們現在要比任何時候都團結才行
Not when we need each other like no other time before.
快跑
Move!
酷斃了
Wow. That's awesome.
就像使命召喚里的場景  你覺得呢
That looks exactly like Call of Duty, doesn't it?
好了  要求是  禁止發布新聞
All right. Here's the deal. No press release.
不要當地法律機關和新聞媒體參與
Keep local law enforcement and media off-site.
設立4.8公里的隔離和禁飛區
Get a three-mile cordon, ditto the no-fly zone.
派一支清理小隊過去把該死的模板找回來
Get an agency scrub team out there and get me the goddamn plates back.
德國警方已經把你手下所有人都監禁在了孔希斯銀行大樓
The German police have your entire team in custody in the Konigsbank Tower.
那不是我的人  是史密斯他們的  我單干
I don't do teams, babe. That's Smith's bag. I'm strictly a solo act.
美 國 大 使 館
我喜歡輕裝出行
I like to travel light.
像忠誠這種東西  我可不帶
Stuff like loyalty doesn't fit in the overhead bins.
我以為你和史密斯是同伙
I thought you and Smith were working together.
你錯了
You thought wrong.
我們是有武器  但你也管不著
Yes, we have weapons. No, you may not wand us.
你想要做交易嗎  那就提條件吧
If you want to deal, we can deal.
讓我費盡心思使你一敗涂地
How about l dedicate my immediate future
如何
to destroying yours?
你怎么不聰明一些
How about you get smart and start dealing
在別人出手之前  先下手為強呢
before somebody else does?
前任上尉
Former Captain.
除非你有像這樣的文件
Unless you've got a piece of paper that looks exactly like this one,
不然這個不合作的麻煩家伙歸我管
then this troubled young loner belongs to me.
我們走
Let's go.
他們到底怎么搞來的引渡令
How the hell did they get an extradition order?
抱歉  帕克  至少我們按規矩辦事
Sorry, Pike. At least with me, there are rules.
中情局也有規矩  比你們更高級而已
CIA's got rules. Our rules are just cooler than yours.
-走  -林奇
- Go.  - You know, Lynch,
要是我把你關在這間屋子里  那可是做了一件大好事
if l could seal this room with you inside, l'd be doing the world a big favor.
那可不好
That's not nice.
是林奇干的  肯定是他
Lynch? Had to be.
離火近一些  弟兄們
Stay close to the fires, boys.
要是那架武裝機還在附近  那也測不出我們的體熱
lf that gunship is still around, it won't read our body heat.
林奇個傻逼  這么心急要干掉我們  根本沒想要確定模板的位置
That idiot Lynch, so quick to kill us, didn't even bother locating the plates.
我們現在還能不用武力嗎  怪頭
Where do we stand on the non-violence now, B.A.?
你生氣了嗎  你是該生氣
You pissed? You should be.
現在模板有屁用  只有莫里森能幫我們洗脫罪名
Who gives a shit about the plates? Morrison was the only way to clear us.
沒有了莫里森  一切都無濟于事
And without Morrison, we got nothing.
-我們怎么辦  頭兒   -我不知道  默多克
- What do we do, boss?  - I don't know, Murdock.
-我不知道  -我知道
- I don't know.  - I do.
林奇個混球  我想我知道怎么對付他了
This guy Lynch, I think I got him figured out.
-你有計劃了嗎  小子  -我們怎么離開這兒
- You got a plan, kid?  - How do we get out of here?
給我二十分鐘先
Give me 20 minutes.
所以莫里森和史密斯那伙人都死了
So, Morrison's dead. Smith and his team are dead.
15分鐘后我們就能找到印刷模板
Another 15 minutes or so, we locate those engraving plates.
你在幸災樂禍嗎
What is this? Are you gloating?
不  我是在打擊你  誰讓你們背叛了我
No, this is me beating you after you burned me.
-我們做了交易  記得嗎  -我們沒做交易
- We had a deal, remember?  - Not you and me.
-你  我  還有莫里森  -我不是直接和你交易
- You, me and Morrison.  - Not you and me, directly.
所以你倆自己密謀  把我排除在外
And you two collude and cut me out.
你在干嘛  真要在車里殺人嗎
Hey. What are you doing? In the car?
要在車里殺人嗎
Are we doing... Are we gonna do this in the car?
-你來殺嗎  -不是  他來
- You doing this?  - He's gonna do it.
好吧  在這兒死真是不錯
Way to go. That's brilliant, right there.
你要干嘛  他在干嘛  老天
What are you doing? What is he doing?
-天啊  -怎么樣了  凱爾
- Jesus.  - How's it going, Kyle?
-你還好吧  -還好
- You all right?  - I'm good.
老兄  你好個鬼  你在干什么
Brother, you are far from good. What are you doing?
歐版消音器
It's a European silencer.
逆時針裝消音器  你就那樣拿槍嗎
It's a suppressor. Counter-clockwise. You're holding a gun like that?
你以前也像這樣拿槍嗎  你居然能活到現在
You've held a gun like that before and you're still here?
真是奇跡
That's amazing.
-別指著我  -天啊  當作我最后的請求
- Don't point that thing...  - Jesus. Final request,
不要讓這家伙開槍打我
don't let this guy shoot me, please.
如果讓索薩知道我們還活著
So, if Sosa knows we're alive...
她就會相信莫里森也還活著
She'll believe Morrison is alive, too.
但愿林奇還在監聽索薩的通訊線路
Let's just hope that Lynch still has Sosa's comm lines.
我是索薩
This is Sosa.
莫里森將軍在我手里
General Morrison is in my possession.
什么  抱歉  我聽不清  你是哪位
What? I'm sorry. l can't hear you. Who is this?
-還沒干掉他呀  -不是吧
- Okay, this was not well thought out.  - No shit.
看著  我來教你怎么殺我
I mean, look at this. Am I to teach you how to kill me?
幫個忙  好嗎  拿起槍管
Hey, do me a favor, all right? Put the barrel...
拿起槍管對準我的頭
Put the gun flush to my head.
-確定嗎  -對了  就是這兒
- Are you sure?  - There you go, right there.
-子彈會橫穿過去嗎  -在你先打傷其他人之前
- Is that going to go through?  - Before you hurt somebody besides me.
好了  我們沒事了
There you go. We're okay. We're okay.
絕不要反銬住一個坐著的人
Never cuff a man in a seated position with his hands behind his back.
這樣就看不到他的手了
Makes it impossible to see the hands.
太酷了
That was cool.
-你喜歡嗎  -喜歡
- You like that?  - I like that.
非常喜歡
I like that a lot.
你還好嗎  蠢貨
Are you all right, you idiot?
-是的  這一下真帶勁  -給他拷上手銬
- Yeah. It was a good hit.  - Please handcuff him.
我們還要手銬干嘛  不用了
We don't need to use them again. We don't need the cuffs.
你知道自己在和誰說話嗎
Who are you talking to?
-布拉德  要手機還是要槍  選一個  -天啊
- Brad, phone or gun.  - Jesus.
手機還是槍  選一個
Phone or gun. Pick.
-把槍放下  -我沒有背叛你  是莫里森的主意
- Put the gun down.  - Hey, l didn't burn you. Morrison did.
我真想打死你
l really wanna shoot you.
你得聽這個電話  長官
You gotta hear this, sir.
你是史密斯嗎
Is this Smith?
前上校打給前上尉  真有趣
From a former colonel to a former captain,
我知道大約三十秒你就可以鎖定信號
I know I've got about 30 seconds before you lock this signal.
所以聽著  我們可以證明自己的清白
So listen, we can prove our innocence.
好吧  慢點說
Okay. All right. Now, go back.
你剛說你抓了莫里森將軍嗎
Did you say you have Morrison? You have General Morrison?
-是的  -他還活著嗎
- Correct.  - You have him alive?
好得很  所以林奇想殺我們滅口
And well, despite Lynch trying to wipe us out wholesale.
電話里說不清  但莫里森的證詞可以證明我們清白
Too much to explain now but Morrison's testimony frees us
揭發林奇的罪行
and fries Lynch.
沒有模板可不行
Well, not without the plates.
也在我這兒
Also in mypossession.
記住  林奇以為我們已經死了  不要讓他知道
Remember, Lynch thinks we're dead, and I want to keep it that way.
-好的  成交  -給我支筆
- All right. We'll deal.  - Give me a pen.
-何時何地  -給我支筆  有誰有筆嗎
- Where and when?  - Got a pen? Anybody got a pen?
-洛杉磯碼頭  四十八小時后的凌晨  -你還用筆呀
- LA docks, 48 hours, dawn.  - You still use a pen?
我把莫里森和模板帶來
I deliver Morrison and the plates.
作為回報  我要求在民事法庭上重審
In return, I want a retrial in front of a civilian court.
好  成交
All right. We'll deal.
洛杉磯碼頭  四十八小時后見
LA docks, 48 hours from now.
你們若敢耍花招  交易就取消
Any bullshit from your end, and that's it, deal's off.
-找到他了嗎  -沒有
- Did we get him?  - No.
帕克
Pike.
你相信有第二次機會嗎
You believe in second chances?
現在相信了
I do now.
說太多了嗎
Too much?
還好  差點就被定位了
I thought you were spot-on.
該我了
My turn.
小白來電
收好這部手機
Hold on to that phone.
我是索薩
This is Sosa.
你好  美人兒
Hello, beautiful.
謝謝
Thank you.
他們這下原形畢露了  看怪頭那樣
They got the raw end of the deal, didn't they? Look at B.A.
跟個大香蕉似的
He looks like a huge banana.
早上好  朋友
Good morning, my friend.
早上好
Good morning.
你是賓基·拉賓諾維茲神父嗎
Rabbi Binky Rabinowitz?
見鬼  我給錯護照了嗎
What passport did I give you?
你從坦桑尼亞來的嗎  我媽媽也是坦桑尼亞人
You're from Tanzania. My mother is from Tanzania.
-見鬼  -這什么情況
- Oh, shit.  - What the hell happened?
-讓非洲人信猶太教  -這里是六號崗臺
- ...converting Africans to Judaism. - This is station six...
我就是做這些事
Stuff like that.
準備行動  我右邊有三個
Let's get ready to move. There's three to my right.
后面有兩個  東北出口有一個
There's two behind me and one at the northeast exit.
等等
Wait a sec.
祝好
Shalom.
-他在干嘛  -默多克  正在編他的生平事跡
- What's he doing? - It's Murdock. Telling his life story.
上帝在我心
There is a God.
-你會說斯瓦希里語嗎  -你不會嗎
- You speak Swahili?  - You don't?
接下去有的忙了嗎  小子
You got enough to work with, kid?
好吧
We will.
咱現在選擇穿過大西洋
You and l have some major favors moving across the mid-Atlantic right now.
到一艘做黑市交易的深海貨船上去
It's a deep-sea freighter, shipping strictly black-market merch.
我們怎么離開呢
How do we get out to her?
我說的就是一艘普通的舊船
A boat. A plain old boat.
默多克  坐船渡海  太帥了
This is what I'm talking about, Murdock. Traveling the open seas in style.
我就喜歡這種交通工具  沒的比  船這么安全
This is the way l like to travel. classy-like. The way people used to, safe.
還坐什么飛機
We don't need a plane.
博斯克  但愿有一天我們能幫你克服飛行恐懼癥
You know, Bosco, hopefully one day we'll get you over your fear of flying.
什么
What?
這原來不是船呀
Hey, that ain't a boat!
只是今天還不行
Just not today.
默多克  給我記住
Murdock, don't you remember what l said?
-你得自己背他過去了  -你得自己背他過去了
- I said you have to catch him...  - You have to catch him...
-你把他弄昏了之后  -你把他弄昏了之后
- ...after you inject him.  - ...after you inject him.
我錯了
My bad.
見鬼  我的頭痛死了
Damn it! My head, man.
-你最愛的椰奶咖喱橄欖沙司喲   -快給我  傻蛋
- Coconut- curry tapenade, your favorite.  - Give me that, fool.
吐司呢
You get them toast points?
給  吐司這就來了
Voila! Toast points.
你非得又把我弄暈嗎
Y'all knocked me out again, huh?
聽好  把你弄昏的是
Okay, now, the whole injection, knocking out,
漢尼拔和小白
Hannibal and Face.
而我是給你做咖喱橄欖沙司滴
The curry tapenade, Murdock.
但我明明是臉朝地摔倒的
Why do l feel like l fell on my face?
還騙我
Huh? Tell me that.
林奇是個矛盾體
Lynch is a paradox.
默多克  你發現了嗎
Murdock, you done with that?
他本該匿名工作  卻偏喜歡受人關注
This is a guy who needs anonymity, but he loves theatricality.
他是個行政官員  不是個執行者
He's an administrator, he's not an operator.
在哪兒
Where is it?
漂亮
Very nice.
所以他總是盡力遠離現場
So he stays as far away from the point of impact as possible,
絕不會直接參與進去
and never gets his hands dirty if he can help it.
但我們要改變現狀
But we're gonna change all that.
你騙不了一個職業騙子
You can't hustle a hustler, fool.
這玩意不能靠近火星和火苗  甚至閃光燈都不行
No sparks, no flames, not even a flashlight near this stuff.
慢點
Easy, easy.
這家伙絕不會出現在事發現場
This guy is never at the flashpoint of anything.
而是在幕后高枕無憂地暗中操縱
He's safe and sound somewhere, pulling the strings.
媽媽
Mama. Mama.
頭兒  為什么搞得這么麻煩
Hey, boss. Why so many of these damn things anyway?
因為亂花漸欲迷人眼  伙計
Because overkill is underrated, my friend.
所以我們要揭開那家伙的保護繭
So we're gonna bring this guy down to ground level.
媽媽
Mama. Mama.
林奇  這邊
This way, Lynch. Lynch.
他最害怕的一點
The last place he'd ever want to be.
就是自己在眾目睽睽下被揭露真面目
Then you put him on display for the whole world to see.
還有問題嗎
Any questions?
怎么了  頭兒
What's up, boss man?
怪頭
Hey, B.A.
這次任務艱巨吧
It's gonna get heavy, isn't it?
這我也說不好
Well, I can't promise you it won't.
給你讀個東西  就一句
Let me read you something real quick.
以暴力取勝  意味著失敗
"Victory attained by violence is tantamount to defeat,
因為這只是短暫的勝利
"for it is momentary."
甘地
Gandhi.
若是心中存在暴力  就把它發泄出來
"It is better to be violent if there is violence in our hearts,
這要勝過用非暴力來掩飾心中的脆弱
"than to put on the cloak of non-violence to cover impotence."
這是誰說的
Who said that?
還是甘地
Same guy.
甘地從不懼怕為自己的信仰而戰
Gandhi wasn't afraid to fight for the things he believed in.
你又信仰什么  怪頭
What is it you believe in, B.A.?
人生如戲
For life is but an opera
跑調了  是不
It's off, isn't it?
應該唱得更高點是吧
I think it's higher.
還不錯了
No, it's good. It's not that, Murdock.
小白  怎么了
Face, what's wrong? Come on, man.
我也不知道  只是在想
l don't know, man. I'm just thinking past this.
這一路上  我們每次都能全身而退
You know, we've always come back alive,
都虧了老家伙的巧妙計劃
the four of us, 'cause of the old man.
-我知道  -但我不是他
- l know.  - I'm not him.
小白  我知道
Face, l know this.
默多克  我不是漢尼拔
Murdock, I'm not Hannibal.
這次行動誰的犧牲會最大
Who has the most to lose on this, Face?
是我
Me.
但我相信你
And I trust you.
我明白
Yeah, l know,
但是  你就是個瘋子
but you're crazy.
還沒那么瘋
Not that crazy.
洛杉磯港
西漢堡號
所有目標差不多到了
Our eagles may have landed.
大家準備好了嗎
Everybody ready to roll?
收到  第一小隊準備行動
Copy Team one on the move.
收到  第二小隊按計劃行事
Acknowledged. Team to en route.
好啦  大家準備好了嗎
All right, guys, everybody ready?
好戲就要開幕了
Curtain's about to come up.
演出開始
Show time.
史密斯就在那里  盯緊他
That's Smith right there. Watch him.
所有小隊都到位了嗎
Ground team is in position?
準備就緒
Standing by.
已經就位
In position.
一隊狙擊手就位
Shoot Team One. Affirmative.
一號觀測員  10到8點鐘方向
Spotter One. 10-8.
注意聽好了
Let's chattermark on comms for now.
莫里森是首要目標  模板就在集裝箱里
Morrison's the primary tango. Plates are the package.
好了  他在跟索薩通話  把電話轉過來
Okay, okay, he's talking to Sosa. I want this call.
你騙我們  我們說好的
You lied to me, Sosa. We had a deal.
快把那該死的電話轉給我  謝謝
I want that goddamn call in my... Thank you.
是說好了  但我改了主意
We had a deal, but I'm changing the deal.
耍我嗎  索薩
Are you kidding me, Sosa? Are you kidding me?
情況起了復雜的變化  現在不由你了
This is a complicated exchange and you have no play here.
聽著  不然就一輩子
Listen, or remain at-large fugitives
-繼續做你的通緝犯  -哦 不
- for the foreseeable future.  - Uh oh. No! No, no.
行行好  我已經把莫里森和模板帶來了
For God sakes, I've got Morrison here and the plates.
我已經暴露了  索薩  暴露了
I'm exposed, Sosa. Exposed!
我們不在碼頭上交易
We're not doing this on the docks.
給我聽好了  我們絕不會自首
Now listen to me, we're not turning ourselves in.
Now you listen to me, we're not turning ourselves in.
你必須按我的條件來  不然就沒的談
I need you to do it on my terms or nothing at all.
去你媽的  見鬼去吧  索薩
To hell with that, and to hell with you, Sosa!
她背叛了他
Ah. She burned him.
小白  怪頭  我們撤  索薩耍了我們
Face, B.A., we're bugging out. Sosa's jammed us.
默多克  放下十號位的箱子
Murdock, get the chopper down here in 10.
他在轉移他
Okay, he's moving him.
盯緊他  他要轉移了
You got him? He's moving him.
老天爺  你別緊張
For the love of God, relax.
我沒緊張  在轉移了
I am relaxed. He's moving him.
不要這樣  漢尼拔  求你了
Don't do this. Hannibal, please.
-那兒  莫里森就在那兒  殺了他  -等下  他拿了模板嗎
- That's Morrison, right there. Take him.  - Wait, does he have the plates?
模板在史密斯手里  快行動
Smith has the plates. Go now.
-干掉他  他就在那兒  開槍  -我來搞定莫里森  準備射擊
- Take him, he's right there. Kill him.  - I've got Morrison, taking a shot.
剛剛真險  小子
A little too close for comfort, kid.
剛才怎么了
What just happened?
天殺的他究竟想干嘛
What the hell is he doing?
他們人呢  誰來告訴我
Where are they? Somebody talk to me.
見鬼  那東西把他們壓死了嗎
Come on, did that thing crush them or what?
好吧  玩三個塑料杯可比這個簡單多了
This was a hell of a lot easier when it was just three plastic cups.
大家冷靜下來  提高警惕  不要魯莽
Everybody just be cool. Pay attention. No hasty moves.
要打敗林奇那樣的人  有三個關鍵要素
So, you beat a guy like Lynch by drawing him in with three things.
奇了怪了  他們到底要干嘛
What the hell are they doing?
聲東擊西
Distraction.
到底怎么回事
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What is happening?
調虎離山
Diversion.
這是要調虎離山  別亂  目標在集裝箱里
This is a diversion! Stay eagle on those containers.
他們要借此逃跑  快開火
They're breaking for the exits! Open fire!
不要暴露  回撤
Do not engage! Back off!
地面隊伍  開槍
Ground teams, engage!
他媽的
Holy shit!
地面隊伍  開槍
Ground team, re-engage.
你被史密斯耍了  他是想要
You are being played by Smith.
吸引你的注意力  林奇  放聰明點
He's trying to draw your eye line, Lynch. Come on, be smart.
抓住他  抓住他  快去
Take them! Take them! Take them! Take them!
注意塔身還有塔腰  是派克和拜庫斯
Contact! Tower house and bow! It's Peck and Baracus!
還要能全身而退
And division.
這是個陷阱  快撤退
It's a trap! Pull back! Pull back!
-他媽的快離開那兒  -不
- Get the hell out of there!  - No, no, no.
這是怎么了  到底怎么回事
What is happening? What is going on?
這計劃不錯  小子
Nice one, kid.
是派克和拜庫斯
It's Peck and Baracus!
-快開槍  -閉嘴  我知道該怎么做
- Shoot them!  - Shut up! l know what I'm doing.
夠了  小朋友們  該我上了
Okay, paintballers, time to go pro.
怪頭  執行下一步計劃
B.A., get to your secondary position.
好了  扭轉局面的人來了
Okay. Game-changer.
你們該適可而止了
Here's what l think of your best-laid plans.
媽的
Shit!
我的天吶
Jesus Christ!
偉大戰略家史密斯的計謀就到此終止了
So much for the grand scheme, Smith.
他媽的到底怎么了
What the hell was that?
怎么回事  小白
Face, what the hell was that?
他給船身開了個窟窿
Pike hit the ship with a SMAW! He punched a hole in the hull!
那計劃怎么辦
What about the plan?
帕克把計劃給搞亂了  這是意外狀況
Pike just blew up the plan! We are ad-libbing!
博斯克  快走
Bosco, get out of there!
我去找漢尼拔
I'm going for Hannibal.
-掩護我  我去找模板  -遵命
- Cover me. I'm going for those plates.  - Yes, sir.
船要沉了  快走
The boat is going over! Get out of there!
抓緊
Bos, hang on!
天呀
Oh! Jeez!
靠
Shit.
博斯克  帕克占據有利位置  我快沒子彈了
Bosco, Pike's got the high ground. I'm running low on ammo, man.
媽的
Shit!
怎么了  帥哥
How are you doing, handsome?
你的槍還他媽能使嗎
Shit, can you cycle that weapon. Nice work.
戰友和子彈
Jeez, close friends and bullets.
最需要他們的時候都去哪兒了呢
Where are they when you need them?
我和你沒私仇  但看著這兒
Don't take this too personally, but look here,
笑一笑  等著槍響
smile, wait for the flash.
拜庫斯
Baracus.
博斯克
Bosco!
林奇
Lynch.
來吧  林奇
Come on, Lynch.
林奇
Lynch.
出來吧  史密斯  別裝神弄鬼了
Come on, Smith! Stop bullshitting.
來呀  林奇
Lynch. Come on, Lynch.
林奇
Lynch...
你找得到我嗎
Where am l?
來呀  林奇
Come on, Lynch.
林奇
Lynch.
來找我吧  林奇
Where am l, Lynch?
來呀  林奇
Come on, Lynch.
林奇  林奇
Lynch, Lynch, Lynch, Lynch.
林奇
Lynch!
終于找到你了  漢尼拔  你可真難找
There you are, Hannibal. Been looking all over for you.
別以為我是白面小生
Hey, don't let the scarf fool you.
我的泰拳還有兩下子  柔術還更好一點呢  但是
My muay Thai is pretty good. My jujitsu is a little better, but...
我手上這些功夫  比起那些集裝箱啊車啊爆炸啊
You had this whole sleight-of-hand thing going with the containers
裝神弄鬼啊什么的  還真是小巫見大巫
and the cars, and the fireworks. "Lynch, Lynch, Lynch!"
真他媽煩人  但老天給了帕克一個火箭筒
God, that's annoying. But you give Pike a rocket.
你沒想到吧
There's your monkey wrench.
漢尼拔  別這樣
Hannibal, don't do this.
你知道嗎  史密斯  本來一切都照你的計劃進行
You know, Smith, you could have the best recipe in the world...
-你欠我這么多  -可惜你千算萬算
- You owe me that much.  - ...but you drop a few bullets
-漏算一著  -漢尼拔  別這樣
- into the batter...  - Hannibal, don't do this.
-林奇  不要  -漢尼拔  別
- Lynch, no!  - Hannibal, please.
天
Oh, God.
天不遂人愿
...and that cake don't bake.
人證物證  都齊了  這下你有麻煩了
Uh-oh. Your witness, your gun, your problem.
你也算報效祖國了  抱歉
You served your country well. Excuse me.
好久不見  錢先生  我可等死你了
Hello, Ben, where have you been all my life?
漢尼拔  看看  兩成年男子對決
Look at us, Hannibal. Couple of grown men.
你流血了  你居然流血了
I'm bleeding. You're bleeding.
別起來
Don't get up.
操你媽
God damn it!
你的泰拳和柔術都那么差勁  林奇
Your muay Thai is as bad as your jujitsu, Lynch.
你必須靠槍才行
Better stick with a gun.
要是有把裝彈的槍你就死定了
You put a loaded weapon in my hand, I'll put a bullet in your head.
我說過我會殺了你
I told you l would shoot you.
防彈衣救了你一命
Kevlar saved your life.
問題是  要是瞄準你的頭  這玩意還頂個球用
Thing is, it doesn't do much good if I pop you in the head.
我要能與防彈衣合為一體的話可就不一定了
It does if you melt it down.
漢尼拔  別這樣
Hannibal, don't do this.
-漢尼拔  別  -要打敗林奇那樣的人
- Hannibal, please.  - So, you beat a guy like that
有三個關鍵要素
by drawing him in with three things.
-聲東擊西  -怎么回事
- Distraction.  - Whoa, whoa, whoa! What is happening?
調虎離山
Diversion.
全身而退
And division.
在眾目睽睽下揭露他的真面目
Then you put him on display for the whole world to see.
搞毛
What the...
真不錯
That's good.
真令人驚訝
Surprise.
布里斯特工
Agent Burress.
你叫我什么
What did you call me?
文斯·布里斯特工  不是你的名字嗎
Agent Vance Burress? lsn't that your name?
至少我的逮捕令上是這么寫的
At least that's the name I've got on this warrant here,
除非你有和這張一模一樣的
and unless you have a piece of paper that looks exactly like...
真好笑  這是我曾說過的話
That's funny. That's what l said.
以我之道還施我身
She's quoting me.
慢慢來
Easy, easy.
你被捕了  罪名是蓄意制造虛假謀殺
You're under arrest for attempted murder,
以及盜竊政府最高機密的
violations of the Civil False Claims Act,
美鈔模板
and the theft of top secret government engraving plates.
慢慢起來
Easy.
看來這計劃還算順利
l guess the plan went okay,
只是我沒考慮到帕克會把船給炸了
considering Pike did blow up the boat, which l didn't account for at all.
子彈沒打穿呢
Bullets didn't go through.
伙計  覺得怎樣
How are you feeling, man?
不好  很不好
Not... Not good.
-怎么了  -不舒服
- What's wrong? - Not good.
我感覺精神正常了
I feel sane.
早知道我早該往你腦袋上來一槍
I should have shot you in the head a long time ago.
我怎么覺得你害怕了
Is it crazy that I'm feeling your anxiety right now?
我看起來像害怕的樣嗎
Do I look anxious to you?
你覺得我被打敗了嗎
You think I'm beaten?
我只是在流血  沒有流虛汗
I'm bleeding, l'm not sweating.
把他帶走
Let's take him out of here, guys. Go ahead, princess.
腦震蕩和撞傷有什么區別嗎
What's the difference between a concussion and a contusion?
-沒事的  伙計  -默多克  干得不錯
-It don't matter, bro. You tore up.  - Murdock, that was beautiful.
你沒事  頭盔很有用嘛
You were right. The helmet worked.
番茄醬立功了
Ketchup worked great.
你表現真棒  現在感覺怎么樣
You did a great job. You okay?
-還好  -清醒點了嗎
- Yeah.  -  Got your bell rung?
下次還是讓漢尼拔制定計劃吧
Just let Hannibal make the plans next time.
-好吧  -好吧
- Oh. Okay.  - Okay.
你的良心感覺怎么樣  大塊頭
How's the conscience, big guy?
平靜如水
At peace.
別熄火
Keep it turning.
我們要帶走他們
We already got them on the exits.
現在方圓3公里都被封鎖了  -索薩是哪位
- We got a two-mile no-fly zone here.  - Which one of you is Sosa?
-我是  -我要找索薩
- I am. I am. - I need to talk to Sosa.
從現在開始  你的囚犯將遣回
As of right now your prisoner is to be remanded
-聯邦關押  -我有他的逮捕令
- into federal custody.  - l have a warrant for this man.
-現在  -我來告訴你吧  我是醫生
-  As of right now...  - I'll tell you what... I'm a doc.
讓我來治療你  我來幫你
Let me doctor you up. Let me help you out.
你要縫針吧
Do you need stitches? Please tell me you need stitches.
我會幫你縫得很好喲
l can stitch you up really good.
先生們
Gentlemen.
中情局
The Central lntelligence Agency
秉持高度的倫理道德
believes in and evinces a profound moral ethic,
和堅定不移的職業標準
as well as an unshakeable professional standard.
因此  我們為發生的一切
As such, we would like to extend our most sincere apologies
向你們表達最誠摯的歉意
for what's happened here.
-祝你們好運  -你們要帶他去哪里
- Good day and God bless.  - Where are you taking him?
你說誰
Who?
我不知道你的名字
I never got your name.
我叫林奇
My name is Lynch.
果然
Of course it is.
他剛剛是說林奇嗎
Did he just say Lynch?
別碰我
Hey. Do not touch me.
別緊張  伙計們
Take it easy, guys.
所有人都給我退下
Everybody, stand down! Stand down!
-去把拿上模板  -所有人給我退下
-Get those plates. - Everybody, stand down!
-這是命令  給我退下  -你想干什么
- That's an order. Hey, you, stand down. -  What is wrong with you?
中尉
Lieutenant.
長官  你是幾時到的  我不知道
Sir, when did you arrive? l had no idea...
-給我點時間  -遵命
- Just give me a minute.  - Yes, sir.
把你的手拿開  肌肉男
FACE: Get your hands off me, tough guy.
雖然搞得一團糟  但我們好歹拿回了模板
Well, that's one hell of a mess. But we did get the plates.
但不幸的是  我得以逃脫合法監禁的罪名控告你們
Unfortunately, I'm gonna have to charge you all with escaping lawful custody.
什么  漢尼拔  那家伙在說什么
What? Hannibal, what is this guy talking about?
怪頭  雖然是誤判  但我們越獄還是違法的
B.A., we were wrongly convicted, but it's still illegal to break out ofjail.
長官  史密斯他們為這次行動
Director McCready, Smith and his team
立下汗馬功勞
were instrumental in recovering those plates.
但他們仍是十級通緝犯  必須逮捕他們
They're still level-10 federal fugitives and l need that off my desk.
這真他媽扯淡  長官
This is chickenshit, sir.
也許對他們是很扯淡
Yeah, well, you know what? Perhaps for them, it is chickenshit,
但是對你  上尉  我們決定將你重新升為上尉
but for you, Captain, we're re-promoting you to your former rank.
他們馬上會被轉移
So, look, they're gonna be delivered
交給長灘市的聯邦法警
to the U.S. Marshals Service here in Long Beach.
-以最高的安全級別運走他們  -我理解  但
-And there should be a C-5 transport... -l understand, but...
半小時后起飛
...on the tarmac in half an hour.
-這勢在必行  -這很不公平長官
- This needs to be done. - This is really unfair, sir.
-真他媽扯蛋  -我可是胡迪尼大師
- This is bullshit.  - I'm like Harry Houdini.
逃脫術大師
這手銬我很容易就能咬開
I chew through your cuffs.
-起身  前進  進去  -往前走
- Get up. Step up. Get in there!  - Step up!
-行動起來  -等下  停一下
- Let's go. Get moving. - Stop. Wait, stop.
-走  -等等
- Move it. -Wait.
-這太沒道理了  -不用擔心
- This is so wrong.  - It got a little aggressive.
-不用擔心  -現在這樣真的大錯特錯了
- Don't worry about it.  - This is really, really wrong,
我會不惜一切代價來彌補
and I'm going to do everything l can to fix it.
-我相信你  -我真的很抱歉  小白
- I know you will.  - I'm so sorry, Face.
這計劃真不錯  小白
Nice plan, Face.
好個毛  才抓住林奇  結果我們又進了監獄
Yeah. We just traded Lynches, and we're going back to prison.
我們交還了模板  這下能抬頭做人了
We returned the plates. We can hold our heads high.
我們做了應該做的
We did the right thing.
但他們卻這樣對待我們  真他媽的
Yeah, and look what they did to us. This is some bullshit.
他們又拋棄了我們  漢尼拔
They burned us again, Hannibal.
我們相信國家機關  但他們卻恩將仇報
We trusted the system and it turned on us.
記住  小子們  無論表面上看起來多么混亂
Remember, boys, no matter how random things might appear,
本質上總是有計劃存在  小子
there is still a plan. Kid.
我不是故意搶你臺詞  頭兒  不過
Well, l don't mean to steal your line, boss, but...
我就愛計劃圓滿的那一刻
I love it when a plan comes together.
依舊被政府通緝
Still wanted by the government,
但這些戰士們  一次次地神奇逃脫
they survive as soldiers of fortune.
如果你遇到困難
lf you have a problem,
如果你走投無路
if no one else can help,
你要是能找到他們
and if you can find them,
或許就能雇傭
maybe you can hire
天龍特攻隊
the A-Team.